Prologue: Before Departing

Rio’s mother was murdered when he was five years old.

For two years after that, Rio struggled to survive alone in the slums.

For two years, he continued staring down his mother’s death.

He couldn’t look away from it.

Kept thinking about it.

Why did his mother die?

Why was his mother killed?

Why? Why?

He couldn’t understand. He thought about it continuously for the two years he spent in the slums, but he couldn’t understand why. He only had a sense of loss and an anger that intensified day by day.

She was his only family member. He didn’t have anyone else. She was his everything. Someone so precious to him was taken from him before his eyes.

And yet, the man who killed his mother unjustly was still living somewhere out there, enjoying life with a pleasant smile on his face.

It was unforgivable.

Absolutely unforgivable.

It was why he wanted revenge. That feeling never faded.

As time flowed by and he grew older, before he knew it, he had plenty of important people in his life other than his mother. When he glanced around at his surroundings, those same people were watching him.

But even then...

Even with those people as a part of his everyday life, Rio’s resolution for revenge was always close at hand.

Sometimes, the memory would resurface. Fragmented replays of his mother being murdered before his half-conscious state.

Each time it did, a nauseating sense of irritation swelled within him. A hatred strong enough to almost make him forget himself.

The target of his revenge, Lucius, was alive. The die had already been cast. Now that he had faced Lucius and failed to catch him, he couldn’t turn back anymore.

He didn’t feel any regret in being unable to turn back from the path of revenge. It was he himself who decided to push forward down this path when he was in his parents’ hometown. He didn’t care if it was a path of no return. He decided he would proceed anyway. That was Rio’s resolution. There was no way he’d feel any kind of regret over it.

That was why Rio tried to discard the people around him. He believed it would be best to stop associating with people if he were to proceed down the path of revenge, and tried to keep Miharu and the others at a distance by pretending to act bad. If he could distance himself from the ones close to him, he would surely be able to give up on everything other than his plans for revenge.

By discarding everything, he could move forward. He wanted that kind of strength. That was the strength Rio formerly had—the strength of being a man with nothing to lose.

Humans were ugly and not worth salvation. Rio thought he knew this, having grown up in the slums by himself after his mother had been killed.

He thought he knew the terror of trusting others and the terror of being betrayed. After all, he knew that he was on the ugly side. That’s why he was afraid of socializing. He was afraid of trusting. He’d always been that way.

That’s why he was constantly one step away from everyone else in order to observe things from a distance. So that he wouldn’t be hurt if he were ever to be betrayed. However, that caused him to feel a sense of alienation. Each time he felt happiness being surrounded by his friends, he felt like this wasn’t the world he should be living in.

Someday, he was going to leave.

However...

He couldn’t simply discard them in the end.

Humans weren’t that ugly.

Because he had realized that... Because he had been taught that...

He started to yearn for it.

To live in an ideal world that had the possibility of myriad risk.

Was it possible for someone like him to be allowed there? That was what he yearned for, even though it was contradictory to yearn for something that was right before him.

However, you can only yearn for what you don’t have. The further out of reach it is, the stronger that feeling. For Rio, his friends were far, far out of reach.

That was why he had tried to keep an objective view, and yet...

If he didn’t want to lose them, he shouldn’t have pursued a life of revenge from the beginning...

Was that a weakness?

A type of naivety?

He didn’t know.

However, there was one thing he did know.

And that was...

That he had to finish this fight as soon as possible.

Rio had a vague feeling that he would be confronting Lucius soon.

◇　◇　◇

Before Rio had left Celia and Aishia for the Proxia Empire, he’d temporarily stepped out of Rodania to visit the stone house hidden in the forests of the outskirts.

His return delighted everyone present, and they relocated to the living room where he was given a warm welcome surrounded by the girls.

“I’m sorry to bring this up on such short notice, but I’ll be leaving on another journey in a few days. I won’t be back here for a while,” he brought up awkwardly.

“...” Instantly, the girls exchanged looks with each other. They had a feeling this would happen; they’d discussed the possibility while Rio wasn’t around.

“I’ll be going to the Proxia Empire,” Rio informed them.

“Are you chasing after that Reiss person?” Orphia asked hesitantly.

“Yes. It’s possible that Lucius, the man who killed my mother, is there...so it may turn into a journey where I kill someone.”

Rio purposefully phrased it this way in order to address his plans for revenge.

“...”

What do they do if Rio formally brings up the topic of revenge himself? The girls had discussed this in advance, but now that it was actually happening they were still unsure of how to react.

“I’ll be coming back...I think. But I’m not sure how to say goodbye in a situation like this. Even if I openly declare I’m going to kill someone, I’m sure everyone will just be bewildered...” Rio said in a troubled and inarticulate tone.

“We won’t stop you,” Sara said stiffly but clearly. She looked around at Miharu, Latifa, Orphia, and Alma’s faces as she continued solemnly. “We’ve talked about it between ourselves already—about how you’re trying to enact revenge on the person who killed your mother. Everyone knows about it. You’re more kind and honest than anyone else, and that’s exactly why you’re strong. But because you’re the way you are, you’re unable to forget your past and carry all your burdens yourself—and so you try to enact revenge as the answer.”

Rio’s face twisted with guilt. “I’m not as impressive of a person as you think.”

He simply wanted to kill him because he hated him. However, he didn’t want to become the same as Lucius, a man who lived like a beast.

It had nothing to do with his own character, but it was a part of himself he didn’t want to lose.

Miserable and pathetic as it was, this was his tiny form of resistance. That’s why he forced down those emotions and irritation in order to act rational.

“I’m sure you’ve experienced greater grief than we can imagine. That’s why we won’t stop you. We cannot stop you. We believe that you surely understand everything and have nevertheless decided to challenge that man to a life-or-death battle...”

There was no way she could easily tell him it was better to give up on his goal of revenge. The reasons that they could come up with for giving up would have definitely crossed Rio’s mind already.

“Everything Sara said is our collective opinion.”

“So please make sure you return. We’ll be waiting in this house.”

Sara’s opinion was the opinion of everyone in the house, so Orphia and Alma immediately spoke up in agreement.

“You have to come back, Onii-chan. You’re not allowed to go wandering off afterwards. Got it?” Latifa demanded and hugged Rio’s arm tightly.

“I’m not a child, you know.” It was as though she was worrying for him like a lost child. Rio had a frown on his face.

“But it sometimes feels like you’ll wander away somewhere. Even when you’re nearby, it’s like you’re far away...” Unable to express her words well, Latifa looked a little frustrated.

“R-Really...?” Rio replied a little awkwardly, feeling slightly startled.

“Really. You wander around alone, and you don’t talk about yourself unless you’re asked—just like with your revenge thing. We know that this is the answer you came to after worrying and worrying over it, so we all decided to see you off. But the truth is, everyone wants to know what you’re thinking, and we’re worried,” Latifa said directly.

“Latifa...” Rio was a little taken aback by the way she addressed the core of the matter, but Latifa’s words seemed to resonate deeply in his chest. He suddenly looked around at Miharu and the other girls and noticed they were all staring at him with watchful expressions.

“I’m sorry. I’ve always been running away. I was sure that everyone would deny my existence... But that wasn’t the case. Even when you learned that I’m trying to kill someone, you’re all still here. That’s why I wanted to talk to you all properly before departing. That’s why I’m here today,” Rio confided in them with a determined look. He had already told Celia and Aishia the things he was about to reveal to them before coming here. Now he was about to tell them the same.

“Are you sure? You don’t have to force yourself...” Sara and the others exchanged looks of hesitation.

“It’s easy to not force myself and run away from everything painful. I’m a dishonest person, so I always try to flee right away, but my problems will never be solved if I keep running from them. I realized that wasn’t the answer. That’s why I want revenge. And I don’t want to run away from everyone either. I don’t want to hide things and distance myself—that’s why if everyone will listen to me, if anyone has anything to ask, I want us all to talk it out,” Rio looked at everyone present and stated.

“Does that mean...that revenge is something painful to you?” Sara asked quietly.

“Resenting people is draining, after all. That’s why the truth is... If possible, I don’t want to take revenge. That’s why part of me thinks that. Part of me also thinks that if I can live a life without hurting others, then that’d be for the best. Once I use my power for hatred, that hatred will come back and leave me walking through a swamp of my emotions forever...”

The girls listened attentively to Rio’s bitter words.

“It’s only natural that what goes around comes around, which means there’ll be no end to it. That’s why somewhere down the line, someone has to refrain from seeking revenge. I understand this as well, but...” Rio continued. “I know. I know that there’s an enemy I have to defeat no matter what,” he declared, showing a glimpse of his resolute will.

“...”

Sara and the others were overwhelmed by his spirit and swallowed.

“There are people out there who calmly—no, gleefully rob others of what’s important to them. I have to fight people like that or I’ll lose everything. They’ll unreasonably try to force you to surrender whatever happiness you have. That’s why I have to fight. Fight...and kill him. In order to prevent any more important things from being stolen from me... That is the reason I want to take revenge.”

Though he seemed cold on the surface, the passion he carried deep within his heart could be glimpsed from between Rio’s words. He wasn’t going to punish him under the name of justice. He simply hated the person who robbed him of something important, and didn’t want to be robbed anymore, so he couldn’t let him run free.

“You’ll fight to prevent any more important things from being stolen... Isn’t that different from getting revenge because your mother was killed? It’s like your motive has changed,” Alma pointed out.

“It’s the same thing. In the end, my motive is my hatred for the enemies who try to steal from me. The feeling of hatred for that man and my desire to kill him hasn’t changed. But I guess you could say I’m no longer trying to take revenge just because my mother was killed...” Rio trailed off inarticulately here. He looked a little worried, which made the girls incline their heads as they watched him.

“I don’t want to drag everyone into the chain of hatred between me and that man. There’s no guarantee you won’t be dragged into things if I fight him. That’s something I want to avoid at all costs. That’s why I have to finish things quickly.”

In order to end this chain of hatred, one of them had to die. Both of their existences were a hindrance to the other.

Because of that, killing was the only answer.

That was, by no means, justice.

It was murder.

“The chain of negativity may end if I kill that man. But it may not end... I might end up dragging everyone down into the swamp with me just by being nearby. Although that may be avoidable if I distance myself from everyone...”

“That’s absolutely not allowed!”

Miharu, Sara, Orphia, Alma, and Latifa’s voices overlapped.

“I considered doing that up until a while ago... I believed even if nothing remained, it’d be easier to be alone. I thought it would be best for me to disappear,” Rio said. The girls gazed at him disapprovingly.

“Hmph.” Latifa strengthened her hold around Rio’s arm, as though to stop him from escaping.

“But I don’t think that anymore. I want to try going down the hard path—is what I started to think. It may not be easy, but I’m sure it will be more fun that way,” Rio added with a pained smile. The girls seemed to be satisfied by this and nodded contently.

“The aura around you has changed a little, Rio,” Orphia pointed out with a giggle.

“You think so?” Rio inclined his head in embarrassment.

“Yes. It’s like you’ve grown a little softer during your time living in Rodania. Does it have something to do with your change of heart?”

“Who knows? It may be because the peaceful days have been in abundance lately... But the trigger for my change in thinking was probably Miharu, Satsuki, and Masato,” Rio said, looking at Miharu.

“Huh? M-Me?” Miharu, who hadn’t been actively participating in the conversation, flinched in surprise.

“Yes. Because the three of you told me your feelings so directly while we were in the Galarc Kingdom. I learned that it was important to tell people your feelings,” Rio said with a faint smile.

“Oh... No, I should apologize for being so audacious back then.” Miharu ducked her face in embarrassment. She had remembered the moment she unexpectedly confessed to Rio in the Galarc Castle.

I love him. I love him, so I want to be together with him. I fell for the same person twice—the Haru-kun he was reborn from, and Haruto now.

The words that had come out of her own mouth replayed in her head. Aishia had connected a path between Miharu and Rio to share the conversation Miharu had with Takahisa.

Aah, I can’t believe he was listening to that. Ai-chan...

There was nothing she could do about it now. Having her feelings conveyed was probably something she should’ve felt happy about, but she couldn’t help feeling embarrassed. Fortunately, Rio was away more often than not after they’d left the Galarc Kingdom, but when they did meet up like this, they were both at a loss for what to say to each other.

Miharu was a shy person to begin with. It didn’t really cross her mind when she was with the others, but even then she was nervous whenever they met again after a long time.

I wonder why... Why am I more nervous than before?

Her heart wouldn’t stop pounding because she was aware of it now.

“Ever since she came back from the banquet, Miharu sometimes looks like she’s remembering something and acts all weird,” Latifa giggled teasingly.

“I-I’m not acting weird, and I’m not remembering anything. Forget about me. We’re talking about Haruto right now, no?” Miharu tried to restore the derailed conversation in a fluster as she blushed.

Chapter 1: The Royal Siblings’ Ordeals

One early afternoon, three days after Rio fought Nidoll at the Proxia Castle, in the room of an enchanted airship flying in the skies near the Beltrum-Galarc border...

“Instans Motus.”

By way of the teleport crystal used by three intruders invading the ship, Christina and Flora instantly disappeared from the room.

The intruders used another teleport crystal to suddenly disappear from the scene of the crime. The only one left in the room was Vanessa, who had been stabbed in the abdomen and was bleeding profusely.

The door to the room suddenly burst open.

“Hey! What was that noise?!”

Roanna and the previously sulking Hiroaki stepped into the room. As soon as they saw the ravaged remains of the room and Vanessa lying in a puddle of her own blood—

“Wha...”

Hiroaki’s eyes widened in shock as he fell speechless. He slowly turned his neck to look around the room, but Christina and Flora were nowhere to be seen.

“What is this...?” After seeing the state of the room from behind Hiroaki, Roanna instantly paled.

“H-Hey, what’s the meaning of this...?” Hiroaki’s voice cracked in his flustered confusion.

“Vanessa!” Roanna ran to her in a hurry.

“Urgh... Princess...” Vanessa stared ahead vacantly with unfocused, hazy eyes, letting out a groan.

“She’s still breathing!” Roanna confirmed that Vanessa was still alive. However, the abdomen of her knight uniform was completely soaked with the large amount of blood that had pooled on the floor. At this rate, she would die from blood loss.

“Hey! What happened?! Where are Christina and Flora?! Hey!” In his shock, Hiroaki questioned Vanessa hysterically.

“Ah... P-Princess...” Vanessa murmured quietly.

“Oh no, don’t speak! You’ll die!” Roanna didn’t force her to speak and instead drew the knife from the sheath at Vanessa’s waist. She proceeded to cut open the buttoned-up jacket Vanessa was wearing, then the buttoned shirt below that as well to expose Vanessa’s upper body without reservation.

“H-Hey, Roanna! What are you doing?!” Hiroaki asked in shock as he looked at Vanessa’s half-naked state.

“I’m checking her wounds. The only place she was stabbed was her stomach, but... Th-This is... Cura.”

Roanna used the minimal amount of movement to confirm the wound on Vanessa’s body, then recited the spell to begin healing her abdomen. Was she stabbed by a blade that was then twisted? Her abdomen was gouged into a bright-red pulp.

“Ugh, that’s brutal...” Hiroaki must have felt nauseous, as he paled and looked away from Vanessa.

“I may not be able to save her alone. Sir Hiroaki, please yell down the hallway for help. The attackers may still be on the ship, so make sure you don’t step outside,” Roanna instructed with an ashen face. The fact that they were nowhere to be seen probably meant they had already fled, but the possibility was still there. Despite the circumstances, she wasn’t about to abandon a life that could still be saved.

“R-Right... H-Hey! Is anyone there?!” Hiroaki nodded nervously and headed to the door, where he yelled down the silent corridor in search of help.

“...”

However, no one stuck their heads out of any of the rooms along the corridor. Of course they wouldn’t. All the nearby soldiers had been ambushed and killed by the intruders, then had their bodies shoved into the nearby rooms.

“Hey! Hey! Anyone! What are you all doing?!” Hiroaki continued yelling in distress.

Wouldn’t the attackers come to this room if I yell? Concern surged within him as he yelled, heightening his anxiety by the moment.

“Hey! Hey! Heeey! Why isn’t anyone responding?!” Hiroaki continued yelling anyway, down the corridor of rooms filled with corpses...

“No one’s coming...” he muttered weakly after some time.

“What in the world happened here...?”

No one on board the airship knew the answer to that. It was a short time after that when the surviving crew members noticed the abnormality on board the ship.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in the western side of the Paladia Kingdom, a small kingdom located to the northeast of the Strahl region that was allied with the Proxia Empire...

Having been forcefully teleported by the attackers on the ship, Christina and Flora were currently standing frozen in a dense forest, dressed in their gowns.

“Huh...? Wha?!”

The sudden change in scenery left Flora in clear confusion. Once she understood that they were in a gloomy forest, she immediately drew closer to her older sister in fear.

“...Where are we?”

Christina touched the magic-sealing collar the men placed on her and looked around in a daze. Her eyes wandered, taking in the dense growth of vegetation.

They had been attacked by three assailants on the enchanted airship, so why were they in a forest on the ground? Was this a dream? The cold sensation of the collar said otherwise.

She looked around, but there was no one else in sight. The plants were being stirred by the wind. When she listened carefully, she could hear the cries of birds and beasts in the distance. Her heart thundered in her chest.

The crystal-shaped magic artifact the men threw at us on the airship... Was it enchanted with space sorcery?

Christina was as calm as could be in such an unrealistic situation, desperately racking her brain for an explanation.

Space sorcery was an ultra-high level of sorcery impossible to use with the modern sorcery of the Strahl region, but she had read about the existence of such ancient artifacts during her Academy days, and the sacred stones that summoned the heroes were also said to be enchanted with space sorcery. It would be extremely difficult to explain the current situation in any other way.

However, it was strange that they were teleported all the way here without anyone awaiting their arrival. The men had also said they didn’t know what would happen once they arrived here...

They said that if they wanted to kill us, they would have done so already. They also said the more hardships, the better—are they going to use us as hostages? But there’s no one around...

There were plenty of forces she could think of that would want to use them as royal hostages, but there wasn’t enough information for her to grasp the situation clearly.

“Christina...?” Flora called out, worried by her silence.

Christina smiled gently to calm her down. “Sorry, I was trying to figure out the situation. Even I am confused by something like this.”

“Where are we? Vanessa, Sir Hiroaki, Roanna... Everyone else on the ship is...” A dark shadow fell over Flora’s face.

“The enchanted airship was still flying normally, so the people in the cockpit should be safe. Sir Hiroaki and Roanna too, surely. Someone will find Vanessa and give her treatment. So...let’s focus on ourselves for now.”

Christina hugged Flora close to her and petted her head softly. Her words weren’t directed at her little sister, but rather at herself.

Either she was still shaken, or she could feel a vague sense of danger from this unpredictable situation, as her hand was shaking faintly.

“Okay...” Flora nodded slowly.

“If we wait here, those men and their allies may appear... But we won’t let ourselves fall into their hands so easily. Before we set off haphazardly, let’s explore this area first. We may find some kind of clue.”

Thus, the two of them began to explore their immediate surroundings. Then, within a few minutes—

“There’s a cabin over there, Christina!”

“Yes, I can see it.”

They discovered a single cabin standing alone in the forest not far from where they were teleported to.

It’s close to the spot where we were teleported to. It would be natural to assume that this place belongs to those men, but...

There may be people inside. If not, then there was still a high chance of obtaining some clues Christina thought as she stared at the cabin.

“We’ll examine the state of things from outside, and if it doesn’t seem occupied, then we’ll look inside. Follow behind me quietly.”

“Okay.”

Glancing around at their surroundings warily, the two of them approached the cabin.

Dresses and high heels. It wasn’t an outfit that was appropriate to walk through the forest in, and it was extremely conspicuous, so it wasn’t suited for moving stealthily. In the first place, the unstable footing of the forest was extremely difficult to walk on. Despite that, they drew within ten meters of the cabin.

“I’m going to get a little closer. You hide here,” Christina said, approaching the cabin alone. She went around the back instead of the front and listened carefully.

I don’t hear anything.

There was no sound of conversation, creaking floors from footsteps, or any type of work being done. There was only complete silence.

The window’s closed, but...

Christina tried to pry open the small, wooden window that was situated slightly above her head. Then, with a quiet creak, the window opened. She stretched upwards to peek inside the room.

There’s no one here.

The light was turned off so the room was dim, but she could see a table and chair.

Christina went around the outside of the house and opened the windows to carefully check the state of the interior. As a result, she confirmed there were no lights on in any room and the cabin was truly uninhabited.

“Flora, come here.” Christina stood before the entrance and called Flora over from the shadows of the trees.

“Was there no one inside?”

“Yes. I feel ashamed for acting like a burglar, but let’s go inside. The door’s unlocked. Right now we want as much information as possible—as well as the supplies that we’ll need to survive being in this forest.”

“Okay...” Flora must have felt some sense of guilt, as she nodded hesitantly.

“I’m opening it now.”

Christina gripped the doorknob and slowly pulled open the door. It creaked louder than when she opened the windows. Even knowing that there was no one inside, the two of them still flinched faintly.

Once they opened the entrance, there was a room that appeared to be like a dining room and a kitchen.

“Let’s go inside.” Christina stepped in first, followed by Flora.

“Pardon the intrusion...”

“Flora. Can you use magic to make some light?” Christina touched the magic-sealing collar and asked.

“Yes! Radialem.”

Flora immediately held out her hand and recited the spell. A geometric patterned spell formula appeared past her hand, turning into a ball of light. It had no destructive power, but it was magic developed to illuminate the dark like this. The brightness of the light could be adjusted by the caster, and it also emitted a faint heat that could be used to warm oneself.

“Let’s check that all the rooms are empty, just in case.”

“Okay.”

It wasn’t a large building. There was a dining area and kitchen immediately beyond the entrance, a bedroom with three beds, a small room for storage, and a toilet. It didn’t take long for them to go through every room and check that it was completely deserted before returning to the dining room.

“It does seem well-maintained...” Christina muttered. She had touched the bed and other furniture and none were covered in any dust.

“Does that mean someone is living here?”

“That, or it’s possible those men anticipated we would find this cabin and had their friends clean it in advance.”

“...” Flora’s face stiffened as she fell speechless.

“Sorry for scaring you. The dining room, kitchen and bedroom are all neat and lack that lived-in feeling, so I don’t think anyone’s living here right now. Though we still can’t relax too much...” Christina said with a troubled look.

“Wh-What should we do?” Flora asked in a panic.

“There’s nothing we can do. I feel bad if this cabin belongs to someone unrelated to those men, but we’re going to rummage around for any food or useful supplies. Come over here.” Christina headed towards the kitchen first. She opened the cupboard to find some simple kitchen utensils and tableware. There was also firewood.

“It looks like there’s a set of kitchenware here. All that’s left to figure out is if there’s food or not. Let’s check the storage room.”

“Okay.”

The two of them moved to the storage room.

“I’ll look through everything. You just stand there and illuminate the room,” Christina instructed quickly.

“Okay.”

Flora’s light filled the room as Christina opened the lid on one of the wooden boxes. Inside was preserved food like dried meat and dried bread, a bottle of oil, jars of seasoning, and bottles of alcohol. In another wooden box, there was a single piece of paper with writing on it.

“A letter...?”

Christina moved beside the light Flora held up to read the letter.

This is food. It hasn’t been poisoned, so feel free to help yourselves. The forest is filled with prowling beasts like bears and wolves, but you should be safe if you stay inside the cabin.

“It looks like this cabin really does belong to those men... It seems like they prepared the food in here for us. It says it’s not poisoned, but...” Christina looked down at the goods and muttered with a tormented expression.

They had been sent here alive through a teleportation artifact. There was no reason for the men to go out of their way to poison them to death after doing that, so it probably wasn’t a lie—but their intent was still unclear.

Of course, it seemed clear they were being kept as hostages, but why were they left unattended in the forest? It made sense to throw them in the forest to make it harder for them to move, but wasn’t it a bit too deserted here for that? Was it possible that this wasn’t an organizational crime? Such doubts arose.

“If there are ingredients, then we can make meals out of them. It looks like learning how to cook in Rodania was the right move,” Flora said to uplift the dark atmosphere. Normally there would be no need for two princesses to learn how to cook, but to make up for the time they spent apart, the siblings had used their days off to learn how to cook together.

“We won’t be able to make the best use of our cooking skills with the ingredients here, but it’s a lot more reassuring than having never cooked before.” Christina set aside the problems she couldn’t solve right now and nodded with a chuckle.

“It said we’d be safe as long as we’re inside this cabin.” Flora looked over at the letter.

“Indeed, if we only considered our own safety, the most pragmatic option would be to stay still in this cabin, but...”

Those men would eventually catch them if they remained here in the cabin.

The journey with Sir Amakawa as an escort taught me that traveling isn’t just about walking. I can’t even fight properly with my magic sealed right now, so I need a trustworthy escort.

However, they didn’t even have the money to be able to stay at an inn. They couldn’t hire an escort to return to Rodania, and all the fighting would have to be left to Flora. It’d be one thing if they were currently within the restoration’s sphere of influence...

If only her magic hadn’t been sealed... Christina touched the magic-sealing collar with an irritated expression as she was lost in her thoughts.

On top of that, they were in the forest. There was no telling what dangers were out there. From the perspective of an older sister thinking about her sister’s safety, they should stay in the cabin, even temporarily.

However, thinking as royalty, she believed they needed to leave the cabin. Though there were dangers in relocating, their freedom of mobility meant they should move for the good of their kingdom. That was the duty of royalty.

Flora saw the pained expression on Christina’s face and guessed at what her sister was thinking. She clenched her fists in a show of enthusiasm. “Christina! I’ll do my very best!”

“Flora...”

Perhaps the men had sealed her magic to prevent them from taking the option of escape, since Flora clearly looked like she wasn’t cut out for fighting. However, Christina had no choice but to rely on Flora.

“If we try to escape from the forest, I’ll be a burden on you because this collar seals my magic. If a beast attacks, all the fighting will be left to you. Do you understand?” she asked.

“Yes.” Flora gulped, but still nodded firmly.

“All right... Then let’s finish our preparations in this cabin and try to leave the forest. After that, we’ll find out where we are and aim to return to Rodania,” Christina decided. But just at that very moment...

Grrr.

The sound of a hungry stomach rumbled cutely. The source of the sound was obviously from one of them, so it was easy enough to identify.

Christina looked at Flora’s shocked face.

“Th-That’s not what you think it is!” Flora held down her stomach and blushed bright red.

“We departed from the Galarc Kingdom in the morning, and it’s already long past lunchtime. Let’s finish eating here first,” Christina said with a chuckle. Thus, they finished their meal before preparing to leave.

◇　◇　◇

Afterwards, Christina and Flora selected the items they would need for their departure, then set about cooking with the utensils and ingredients in the cabin. They made a soup by stewing grains and preserved meat, seasoned with salt. That way, the dry and stiff bread could be eaten easily once it was dipped in the soup.

There wasn’t much of the work they could split, so Christina did all of the cooking alone. It didn’t take much time, either. She carried the completed dish over to the dining table, where they sat down across from each other.

“Go on, give it a try...” Christina said doubtfully, staring at the dish.

It wasn’t inedible when she tasted it herself, but it was nowhere near as good as the food they normally ate.

“Thank you... It’s delicious, Christina!” Flora spooned the soup into her mouth and beamed happily.

Christina blinked at the look on her little sister’s face, then gave a slightly curt but embarrassed response. “...Is that so?”

I want to protect her smile, Christina thought.

◇　◇　◇

The ironclad rule of traveling was to depart in the morning. However, Christina and Flora set off into the forest after eating lunch. They considered staying in the cabin for a night, but the longer they delayed their departure, the more they’d risk their assailants closing in on them.

Unfortunately, there was no map in the cabin for them to determine their present location, but they were prepared to camp outside if need be. That said, they didn’t just start walking off in a random direction once they’d left the cabin.

“That tree will do.”

Christina first found a tree with a lot of branches that was taller than the other trees around it.

“What’s wrong with that tree?” Flora asked curiously.

“I’m going to see what direction to head in from the top of that tree. If the view is clear, I may be able to see where the forest ends.”

“I see... As expected of you!”

“This is how Sir Amakawa got his bearings while we were traveling through the forest. I’m just imitating him,” Christina said, embarrassed by her little sister’s open praise.

“This is what Sir Haruto did...”

Flora’s expression softened faintly at that name. Christina was pretty sure that wasn’t just her imagination.

“Now, let me try climbing this,” Christina said as she selected a branch she could start climbing from. However, Flora called for her to stop.

“Umm... I’ll climb the tree, Christina.”

“You will...? But you’re not good at physical activities, right?” Christina blinked at the unexpected offer.

“Even so, it’ll be much easier for me to climb once I’ve enhanced my physical abilities with magic.”

“Still...”

Flora’s suggestion made sense, but Christina was hesitant. When she considered the chance of Flora falling, she felt it would be much better for her to climb the tree herself. It was common to see unathletic sorcerers lose control of their magically-improved physical abilities and trip over their own feet. Climbing trees wasn’t particularly strenuous, but it still demanded some degree of coordination, so Christina was worried.

“I’m not as smart as you, so please let me do this much. I’ll be fine.” Flora was oddly assertive for once.

“All right... But don’t push yourself too hard. It doesn’t matter if you feel unsteady and have to stop in the middle. It’ll be too hard to climb in heels, so take off your shoes and go barefoot. Climbing in a dress might be tough, so you’ll have to put up with this even if it’s improper.” Christina hesitated before nodding, then rolled up Flora’s dress and tied it with a rope taken from the cabin so that it wouldn’t get in the way of her climbing.

“Okay! Augendae Corporis!” Flora replied in high spirits, taking off her shoes and reciting the spell. A geometric spell formula immediately engulfed her body—proof that her physical abilities had been enhanced.

“Be careful, okay? Use only the thick branches, not the thin ones. You don’t have to reach as high as you can go right away... Just take it slow and steady,” Christina called out to her, a worried look still on her face.

“I know. Here I go, then!” Flora replied with a forced smile, then finally began to climb. She obeyed her sister’s advice faithfully, climbing little by little without aiming too high in one go.

“...” Knowing that calling out to Flora without thinking would just interrupt her concentration, Christina watched her climb in silence.

“Heave-ho... Heave-ho...” Flora grunted sweetly, climbing with her eyes fixed upwards.

It looks like she’ll be all right. But I have to watch over her carefully. Christina vowed to catch Flora if she fell. However, contrary to her worries—

“I did it, Christina! I’m at the top! It’s a wonderful view!” Flora declared.

“Right now, the sun should be climbing from the south, so remember its position. Also, can you see the edge of the forest?” Christina had to raise her voice to speak to her. Flora couldn’t be seen from the ground behind all the branches and leaves, but she was apparently captivated by the scenery.

“I’ve memorized the position of the sun! The other trees are also pretty tall, so I can’t see the edge of the forest... But I can see smoke rising in the distance!” Her voice echoed back down to Christina on the ground.

“There must be people living there... Do you know which direction it is?” Christina muttered the first half to herself, then raised her voice again to ask the second half.

“Umm, the sun’s in that direction, so... It’s to the east, I think!”

“Thank you! Once you’ve memorized the directions, come back down.”

“Okay!” Flora’s cheerful voice echoed back. Not long after, her descending figure could be spotted between the branches and leaves.

“When you’re descending, focus on the branch below you instead of the ground! Make sure you choose your footholds carefully.” It wasn’t as though Christina had any experience in tree climbing, but she gave Flora advice as if she were putting herself in Flora’s position.

“R-Right. Don’t look at the ground, just at the branches...” Flora descended slowly and nervously. She took a considerably longer amount of time climbing downwards than she had upwards, but she managed to make it roughly two meters above ground.

“Looks like it’ll be all right...” Christina said in relief, having watched her in suspense.

“Yes. If I rely on the branches, then this much is... Eek!”

She had just crouched down to dangle from a branch when it snapped. Surprised by the sudden falling sensation, Flora screamed.

“Look out!” At the same time, Christina ran below her. She caught Flora as she fell, but the weight of her fall was too much for her to support. They toppled over together, but she sufficiently fulfilled her role of a cushion.

“Ow, ow, ow...”

Clutched in Christina’s arms, Flora opened her eyes fearfully to her sister’s face right before her.

“Are you okay...?”

“Yes, somehow...”

“I see. Thank goodness.” Christina sighed in relief. They remained hugging each other for a while, lying on the floor in a daze.

“Heh. Heheh. Hugging each other like this in the forest is kind of strange. Let’s get going soon,” Christina suggested with an amused smile.

“Okay.” Flora nodded shyly.

“Your dress is all ragged now. Let’s fix it before we depart. And put on your shoes again.”

Christina stood up and checked Flora’s outfit, undoing the rope to roll down the dress. She also picked up the discarded shoes and made her put them back on. She considered walking barefoot, but that made them liable to being injured by tree branches, so she gave up on the idea.

Incidentally, Flora’s dress must have caught on branches while she was climbing, as it was noticeably ripped and coming apart in several places.

“Thank you very much.” Flora seemed to find something pleasing, as she thanked her with a cheerful grin.

“I haven’t done anything deserving of thanks. More importantly, are you sure you remember the directions? What an odd child,” Christina said awkwardly, picking up their belongings left on the ground beside them. She had made makeshift backpacks using a blanket on the bed in the cabin, filling it with food, seasoning, and cooking utensils.

Perhaps it was because they were dressed in gowns with high heels, but their appearance would have looked extremely mismatched and comical to an onlooker. Thankfully, there were no spectators to worry about here.

“Yes! The sun was in that direction, and the smoke was rising in that direction!” Flora picked up her own backpack and pointed at the locations she memorized.

“Well done. Let’s get going then.”

The two set off in order to escape the gloomy forest.

◇　◇　◇

How much time had passed since then? The forest floor was difficult enough to walk on to begin with, yet the two of them had to proceed in fancy high-heeled shoes unsuitable for walking. Their expensive gowns were already stained with dirt at the hems.

Their feet were heavy and riddled with blisters, so Flora occasionally cast healing magic over them to temporarily ease the pain as they progressed. However, the sun was beginning to set and the forest was getting much darker. Their conversation diminished as time passed.

I can’t see the end of the forest at all. How long have we walked? I doubt she got the direction wrong, but... Christina thought as she silently moved her feet, glancing at Flora walking beside her. Flora’s expression clearly showed her fatigue.

Christina’s field of view was filled with the same trees they’d been looking at all day. When they had first set off she could see into the depths of the forest, but now it was too dark to see very far.

She hadn’t intended on taking the forest lightly, but she had expected them to make it out today, which was why their current situation made her mentally and physically exhausted.

“Let’s stop here for the day. We’ll eat, have a good night’s sleep, then prepare ourselves for tomorrow.” Christina decided to make camp before the forest became completely dark. It was another ironclad rule of traveling to set up camp before it became dark when one couldn’t reach their destination by sunset.

“Okay.” Flora replied with a sigh that expelled her fatigue.

“Where should we sleep? Well, the only option we have is the trees.”

She looked around, but there was no flat land. Small stones were also scattered about the place, making it difficult to sleep on the ground. It seemed that sleeping against a tree would be for the best.

“Did you camp outside while traveling with Sir Haruto, Christina?” Flora asked.

“No. Sir Amakawa managed our travel time and route appropriately so that we never had to sleep outdoors.”

She had been impressed back then too, but looking back on that time in her current situation made her appreciate how amazing that was all over again.

Just then, Flora’s stomach let out a cute grumble of hunger. One beat later, Christina’s stomach echoed that sentiment.

“Shall we eat, then?”

The two of them giggled in amusement and set about eating dinner.

◇　◇　◇

That night, in the middle of the dark forest which had fallen completely silent, Christina and Flora sat under a tall tree, wrapped in the blankets they took from the cabin, and huddled before a campfire.

There must have been nocturnal beasts in the forest, as their eerie cries in the distance made Flora tremble. At first she had been too terrified to sleep, but the fatigue she accumulated eventually won over, and now she was dozing off with her head resting on Christina’s shoulder.

“Flora, you must be exhausted. Go to sleep already,” Christina said to her sleepy sister.

“But what about you, Christina...?” Flora’s drowsy eyes were filled with worry. Her older sister had stayed awake this entire time because Flora couldn’t sleep.

“I’ll sleep as soon as you fall asleep. If you’re feeling drowsy, you should be able to fall asleep quickly.”

“Okay. Thank you.”

“Good night.”

“Yes, good night...” Flora must have approached her limit, as she passed out as soon as she replied, leaving Christina as the only one awake.

I can’t believe we’re camping in the forest. I did learn a little about camping while at the Academy, but...

The information had mostly been targeted for royalty and nobility. Like how to order people around, what kind of place was suitable for camping with a large number of soldiers, and so on. Although she had participated in an outdoor drill as part of her lessons on military operations, those drills were merely for form’s sake, as all the personnel, equipment, and the testing ground had been prepared in advance.

However, an extremely irregular situation had occurred in her sixth year... Christina recalled the outdoor drill she participated in when she was twelve years old. They left the route that had been provided to them and, as a result, were attacked by monster swarms that would have otherwise been exterminated. In the end, they were even attacked by a minotaur and narrowly avoided a disastrous incident.

If Sir Amakawa is the same person, then...

There were two people that immediately came to Christina’s mind. One was the orphan, Rio. The other was the honorary knight, Haruto Amakawa. No matter how much she tried to discard her conviction that the two were actually the same person, she always returned to the same thought.

If Haruto Amakawa were here right now, she probably wouldn’t feel any fear about her current situation. Though she knew this wasn’t a good thought to have, Christina couldn’t help thinking this way.

She knew she wasn’t a very capable person, but she couldn’t even use magic right now. The fear of whether she could protect Flora was overwhelming. And she was fully aware of how self-centered, convenient, and spoiled this wish was...

Why do I keep hoping for him to save us from this situation...?

Someone like her should have been even less than a complete stranger to him. Haruto Amakawa directed his kindness towards Celia, whereas Christina had only received the leftovers of that. With that thought, she scoffed at herself with a hint of deeply seeded guilt.

I have to do my best to get Flora back to Rodania...

Christina softly petted Flora’s sleeping head. That seemed to release her strained nerves, causing a sudden surge of sleepiness to wash over her.

She had continuously strained herself thinking she had to be strong for her sister, so she was actually fairly exhausted. Unable to fight against the drowsiness any longer, Christina fell into a deep sleep as well.

◇　◇　◇

The next morning...

Sunlight had just started filtering faintly through the trees. Despite the uncomfortable sleeping environment, Christina and Flora slept through the night without waking up even once. The forest was cold as they slept and their quality of sleep wasn’t the best, but they both got enough hours of sleep.

The sisters blinked their eyes open. The first thing that came into view was the forest scenery, followed by the sight of the other with their eyes closed tiredly. Then, as their own fatigue from walking hadn’t recovered, they soon closed their eyes for a second round of sleep, surrendering themselves to the warmth of their blanket. They wanted to rest a little longer, unable to resist that desire. They half-dozed, with only the smallest bit of stimulation needed to wake them next time.

“Mm...” At the sensation of something tickling her neck, Flora woke up first.

What...? Flora thought, reaching for her neck.

“Oww!” A sharp pain pricked the back of her neck, making her flinch.

“Wh-What?! What happened?” Flora’s sudden scream shocked Christina awake.

“Th-There’s a pain in my neck...” Flora said, brushing her hands at the place where she felt the pain in a panic. Something small was sent flying as a result. It was a spider.

“Eek!” she cried out, immediately understanding the situation she was now in and paling more and more by the second.

“N-No! No! No! NO!” She had been bitten by a spider. Thinking there could be more bugs on her body, Flora shot to her feet and started patting herself down in a fluster.

“C-Calm down. It’s okay, I’ll look at it for you.”

“P-Please do...” Christina stood up and patted down Flora’s dress, checking carefully for any bugs. She also checked underneath the dress, confirming that the only bug that had made contact was the spider.

“It’s all right. There are no other bugs,” Christina said in relief.

“Th-Thank goodness... Sorry about that. I screamed out in surprise,” Flora apologized for losing her composure.

“It’s fine. I’d be surprised if a spider bit me in my sleep too,” Christina said with a chuckle.

“I’ll check if there are any bugs in your dress as well,” Flora offered, moving to pat down Christina’s dress to check for any foreign substances attached.

“Before you do that, detoxify the area you were bitten with magic. The spider may have been venomous,” Christina said, looking down at the fleeing spider.

“R-Right! Purgo!”

Flora must have forgotten the possibility of venomous spiders, as she hurriedly placed her hand over her neck and began detoxifying it.

I’ve heard there are some poisons that can’t be detoxified with magic, but...

Christina watched on with a tinge of unease.

Detoxify magic, as its name implied, was magic commonly used to neutralize poisons, but like Christina was thinking, there were some poisons that couldn’t be detoxified. This was because detoxifying magic broke down the substances that were toxic to the human body and made them harmless—it had no effect on bacteria, viruses, and mold.

Medical technology hadn’t advanced enough in this world for people to consider the fact that bacteria and viruses weren’t a type of poison, so they could only explain it away as Purgo being unable to detoxify all poisons.

That being said, it was clear that would only make Flora uneasy for no reason, so Christina didn’t mention it. She could only pray that the detoxifying magic worked, or that the spider wasn’t venomous to begin with.

“Show me the spot you were bitten... Looks like it isn’t bleeding. But cast healing magic over it anyway.”

Christina peeked through the gaps between Flora’s hand casting magic to check on the affected area.

“Okay.”

After Flora activated healing magic like directed, Christina prepared the same menu as yesterday for breakfast. Once they had eaten breakfast and warmed up, the two of them set off to escape the forest.

Chapter 2: Reiss’s Intentions in Rodania

Meanwhile, several hours after Christina and Flora were originally sent to the forest in Paladia Kingdom...

Rodania, the capital of Marquess Rodan’s domain, was home to the headquarters of the Restoration. The Restoration’s central office was located in the guest house, which Celia was visiting. Normally, the leading nobles of the Restoration and their secretaries would be working hard at their duties, but no one answered the door when she knocked.

“Excuse me...” Celia opened the door hesitantly.

There was no sign of anyone else inside the silent office.

That’s weird... Did everyone go out to meet Princess Christina and Princess Flora?

Celia was visiting the central office on the day Christina and Flora were scheduled to return to Rodania from the Galarc Kingdom. She cocked her head in wonder, but it wouldn’t be too strange for everyone to go and greet the two princesses if they had returned already.

That was what she thought, when Aishia suddenly materialized beside her.

“H-Hey, Aishia! You can’t materialize here, even if there’s no one in the room,” Celia scolded her in a fluster. She didn’t think the room would be left empty for long, which meant that someone could come back at any time.

“Step back. There’s a strange presence,” Aishia said, staring at the corner of the room.

“Huh...?” Celia followed her gaze.

The distance between them was a few meters.

“I suppose there was no hiding after coming this close. And as I expected, the one guarding Celia Claire in spirit form was you... I had my hopes up, but it seems I’ve been completely outwitted by that man. What a bother...”

The Proxia Empire ambassador, Reiss, stood there quietly. How long had he been there for? It was as though he had appeared out of nowhere.

“Why do you know about Aishia’s spirit form...?” Celia mumbled with a dumbfounded look.

“I wonder why indeed...” he chuckled smugly.

“What do you want?” Aishia stared at Reiss as she asked him directly.

“Do you think I’d answer that? That’s what I’d like to say, but my purpose isn’t to confront you here—I’m not that rash. I had business with a particular member of the Restoration. Unfortunately, my timing wasn’t the best... It seems everyone in this room has headed for the harbor already.” Reiss shrugged and looked out the window as though to change the topic.

“Business? Who are you after?” Aishia asked in her flat tone, but her gaze was slightly sharper than normal.

“I’m afraid I can’t tell you that much.”

“If it’s Celia you’re after...” Aishia stood before Celia as though to protect her from Reiss. He had already made his hostility clear on their journey from Cleia to Rodania—if he was after Celia, then there was even less of a reason for her to show him any mercy.

“Just to be clear, the reason why I confronted your contract holder on the journey from Cleia to Rodania was merely because of Princess Christina. Well, my plans were foiled and the princess safely reached Rodania in the end, but... As long as you don’t get in my way, I won’t have reason to harm you either.” Reiss raised both his hands to show he had no hostile intentions.

“Why are you after Princess Christina and Princess Flora?” Celia asked with bated breath.

“I’m afraid I can’t answer that either.”

“Is there a spy amongst the Restoration leaders? Is that why you’re here?”

“Who knows?” Reiss evaded Celia’s probing questions with vague answers.

“You said you were outwitted before.” Celia picked up a part of Reiss’s earlier statement to probe him further.

“Let’s leave the unnecessary chatter at that. This situation is extremely unexpected for me, so I’d like to leave as soon as possible.” Reiss ended the conversation there and made to leave.

“Your words cannot be trusted. Therefore, I’m not letting you get away,” Aishia stated quietly.

“Oh? You wish to fight me? In such a restricted space like this? It would be one thing if you let me retreat quietly, but if you’re going to fight, then I will resist.” The room would inevitably be destroyed if they fought, Reiss was implying. “I doubt even you would be able to suppress me easily. Much less while protecting Celia Claire as you fight.”

Reiss looked at Celia.

“I-I can fight a little myself. Did you think we would let you walk away peacefully after you snuck all the way into our innermost office? Even if I set aside the matter of Princess Christina and Princess Flora, you’re still related to Haruto’s enemy.” Despite the nervous look on her face, Celia refuted him without cowardice.

“I haven’t snuck in, though. Since you’ve found me like this and all. And what if I was invited here as a diplomat?” Reiss chuckled while evading the point. As he said that, he approached the balcony of the office.

“If you want to leave the estate, you can leave through the front door and not the balcony,” Aishia said, raising her right hand up at the ceiling. She had already prepared her magic essence for combat, but she instantly increased that essence further. Then, without any visually obvious phenomenon occurring, a screeching ultrasonic sound rang through the air.

“A powerful resonance between ode and mana...?”

While Celia couldn’t use spirit arts as a sorcerer who handled magic, she had lived in the stone house for a long time. Thanks to her training under Rio and the spirit folk girls, she was able to see the light of ode and detect mana. Thus, she understood precisely what Aishia had tried to do. That is, she had forced a powerful resonance between the ode and mana across the entirety of Rodania, creating a signal that could only be noticed by those who could sense it. Sara and the others would soon realize something had happened.

“I see, so you’re going with that... I shall take my leave now, then.”

Reiss immediately guessed that their allies were hiding nearby. If they all joined up together, Aishia would be able to focus on pursuing him alone—something which would be extremely problematic. With an annoyed sigh, Reiss took a great leap onto the balcony and flew into the air with spirit arts.

At the same time, Aishia picked Celia up in a bridal carry. “We’re going to chase that man. Hold on tight to me.”

“Huh...?!” Celia let out a hysterical noise at abruptly being picked up. Aishia accelerated suddenly and flew outside from the balcony.

“W-Wait! Hold on!” Celia screamed.

“Don’t open your mouth while we’re accelerating. You might bite your tongue,” Aishia advised calmly. Flight using spirit arts involved setting up a wind barrier against the surroundings, so that the air resistance was eliminated while flying at high speeds. As a result, one could converse while flying, but the faster the flight, the more recoil would be felt from the acceleration. Aishia could control even that recoil with her spirit arts, but her control wasn’t as accurate with the considerable burden of carrying Celia in her arms.

“G-Gosh, don’t surprise me like that. Though I guess it was an emergency, so it makes sense... But what do we do now?”

Once the recoil of Aishia’s acceleration finally calmed down, Celia pouted her lips cutely. However, she soon put those feelings behind her and focused on chasing Reiss. She could see him fleeing through the air ahead of them, and when she looked down, she could see the city of Rodania below.

“We’ll lead Reiss to the stone house. I’ll attack him from the sides, so use your magic to stop him from moving upwards. You don’t need to hold back. You can use intermediate attack magic spells.”

“A-All right. I’ll give it a go.” Celia gulped and nodded at Aishia’s orders.

“Here we go, then.” Aishia created countless balls of light at her side, each roughly one meter in diameter. The next moment, they all fired outwards and curved in Reiss’s direction.

“As expected of a humanoid spirit. What wonderful control.” Reiss glanced back and evaded the light spheres that curved irregularly.

“I’m not as good as you, but I’ll go all-out on magic essence until Sara and the others arrive as backup! Quintet Magician Magicae Displodo!” She wasn’t about to be a burden like she had been on the journey from Cleia to Rodania. Celia focused all of her mental energy on reciting her spell. Seven magic circles appeared around her; she took a mere three seconds to take aim and fired at just a hair’s breadth above Reiss’s head.

Whoa! Seven intermediate attack spells at once, you say? Her spell deployment is also quick. I didn’t think I was underestimating her, but I see why she’s called the genius sorcerer now. It would be one matter if I was facing her alone, but having a sorcerer of this level as a support is quite troublesome indeed...

Reiss avoided Celia’s light missiles by slightly lowering his altitude, when the next barrage came at him without delay. There were as many bullets as there were spell circles, and as soon as he dodged one, the next would come flying. On top of that, it wasn’t only Celia’s attacks coming at him.

When he tried to raise his altitude, Celia’s magic would snipe at him, and Aishia’s spirit arts freely changed direction to fly at him from the sides.

I’ve been completely blocked from above and to the sides. I can’t accelerate like I want like this. We’ve already left the skies of Rodania, so perhaps it would be better for me to just hide myself in the forest.

Thinking that, Reiss lowered his gaze to the forest.

“Guh...”

Suddenly, an ice, fire, and light bullet came shooting up from the ground. Orphia came flying out of the forest.

This is...a rather unlucky situation. No, I suppose I was led here on purpose. Reiss made a contemplative face at the difficult situation he was in. Just then, Aishia swooped down and approached Orphia.

“Lady Aishia!”

“Orphia, take Celia. Protect the house with everyone else,” Aishia said, tossing Celia in Orphia’s direction.

“Huh? Whaaa?!”

Celia screamed at the sudden floating sensation. However, they were racing against time right now. Reiss had already taken the chance to speed up and retreat.

Chapter 3: Fang of the Avenger

Several months had passed since Renji’s arrival. He never returned to Rhea’s village in the Vilkis Kingdom after that incident, instead acting as an adventurer in the Rubia Kingdom.

For the record, the adventurer’s guild was an international organization established and entrusted by each nation. The original purpose of its establishment was to force a part of the kingdom’s unmanageable defense onto those socially unfit for proper jobs, so that the kingdom could manage them indirectly and effectively utilize them as a labor force.

Of course, it was pretty much an international organization in name only. The organization headquarters existed in form, but there was no base equipped with said function, and management was conducted practically independently by the branches in the capital of each kingdom. This was because the officials of each kingdom were dispatched to supervise the operations of the branch, so they couldn’t cross kingdom borders.

Furthermore, in order to become an adventurer, registration at the headquarters or branch was required, each having its own merits and demerits. For example, belonging to a branch restricted the activities under the jurisdiction of other branches (in this respect, belonging to the headquarters gave one the freedom to act in every branch, but the support from regional branches was weaker).

Renji belonged to a regional branch of the Rubia Kingdom. At first, his impudent personality on top of his small stature and young appearance caused the other adventurers around him to treat him disparagingly and aggressively.

However, he turned the tables on every adventurer that picked a fight with him regardless of their rank, completing very difficult subjugation requests all by himself until, eventually, everyone left him alone out of fear.

Instead, he gained fame as the fastest rising rookie in history, obtaining nicknames like “Aloof” from his solo activities or “Ice Emperor” from his powerful ice enchanted sword (the generic name for weapons with ancient sorcery in them).

His name even spread to the royal castle, reaching the ear of the Princess Knight, first princess Sylvie Rubia. She personally invited Renji to the castle to judge his abilities, sparring with him before scouting him as a personal knight.

“I have no intention of working underneath anyone. Royalty and nobility are especially out of the question.”

Renji brazenly refused Sylvie’s offer to become a knight, but the impudence in his answer showed his lack of understanding of the world. This caught Sylvie’s favor, so they formed a friendship instead of a master and servant relationship.

“Hey, it’s Aloof.”

Simply by appearing at the adventurer’s guild in the Rubia Kingdom capital, the adventurers in the lobby stirred noisily. There were some gazes of strong envy and hatred among them.

“Hmph.” Yet Renji marched through those gazes with a cool smile as he headed to the counter. He didn’t dislike being looked at with envy. It didn’t feel bad being called Aloof and Ice Emperor—he had been behaving exactly as such, after all.

Having forgotten about the events of the village—no, in order to avoid remembering the events that had occurred in the village—Renji continued to enjoy his new life as an adventurer to the fullest.

◇　◇　◇

That was what Renji’s other-world life had been like before everything changed. It was the day after Rio had his fierce battle with Nidoll in the Proxia Castle—two days before Christina and Flora disappeared from the enchanted airship. The first princess, Sylvie Rubia, was visiting the expensive inn room that Renji had rented in stealth.

“Long time no see, Renji.” Sylvie sat down on the sofa across from Renji and smiled.

“You sure about this? Even if you came secretly, you’re still visiting an inn like this,” Renji asked with a chuckle.

“You sure have guts calling the highest quality inn in this kingdom ‘an inn like this.’”

“It’s still not a place a princess can visit so casually, right?”

“Did you not want me to come?”

“Nothing of the sort. I just can’t give you a proper reception.”

“Oh? I’m surprised you understand the concept of welcoming your guests,” Sylvie said cheerfully.

“Who do you think I am? Well, whatever. I haven’t seen your face lately, so I just so happened to be wondering what you’ve been up to as well.” Renji sighed tiredly as he asked about Sylvie’s recent developments.

“Not long ago, there was a banquet in the Galarc Kingdom where the heroes of each nation had gathered. I was away from the capital for a while because I had been invited as the representative of this kingdom. Then there were various things to deal with once I returned, too,” Sylvie answered, her tiredness showing faintly on her face.

“You met the heroes of each nation...?” Renji asked.

“Yeah. I talked to them a little,” Sylvie replied while watching Renji’s face.

“What were they like?”

The rumors that heroes had been summoned across the Strahl region had also reached the Rubia Kingdom, which Renji was already aware of. He had yet to confide in anyone about his status as a hero, but he seemed to be interested in the other heroes.

“...They were boys and girls the same age as you and me,” Sylvie answered simply after a slight pause.

“I see... That aside, has Estelle been well?”

Renji seemed to feel awkward about hiding his own hero status, so he didn’t ask any further questions about them. Instead, he changed the topic to Sylvie’s little sister, the second princess Estelle. The last time he was invited to the castle, Renji had spent some time interacting with Estelle. In contrast to Sylvie, a gallant lady known as the Princess Knight, her younger sister was a modest and mild-mannered girl. It was because of this that they were often said to have polar opposite personalities for siblings.

“...Estelle is recuperating right now.” A shadow fell over Sylvie’s face as she spoke.

It’s a confidential matter of the kingdom. I can’t tell him she was taken hostage as a tool for diplomacy, was what Sylvie was thinking.

“Is she sick?”

“Well, something along those lines.”

“If you need any medicinal herbs, I can go get them.”

“No, it’s okay. She should recover with time, so don’t worry about it. She’ll definitely be able to see you again someday. When that day comes, let’s bring her to this inn,” Sylvie said with a smile to smooth over Renji’s concerns.

“I see...” For a moment, Renji’s eyes were captivated by Sylvie’s smiling face, but he soon chuckled and said, “But Estelle’s a princess. It’d be better for me to go to the castle.”

“Hey... What do you mean she’s a princess? What about me? I’m a princess too!” Sylvie blinked, then objected with a dissatisfied face.

“Yeah, you’re the Princess Knight.”

“Stop that. I don’t like that name.”

“Hey, you were the one who introduced yourself as the Princess Knight when we first met. We even sparred after that, remember?”

“I figured introducing myself that way would lead to a match more naturally.”

The friendly atmosphere over their chat was unthinkable for a first princess and a mere adventurer. Time flew by while they chatted pleasantly.

“It really is nice talking to you like this; there’s no need to be so stiff about it. It’s calming,” Sylvie muttered.

“What’s with you all of a sudden?”

“Nothing. I’ve just had to keep my nerves steeled a lot recently. I was just thinking how it was worth visiting you, as I’ve been feeling pretty burned out.”

“Have you been working too much? It isn’t my place to say this as an adventurer living leisurely, but working too hard is a problem. You should take some time to relax in moderation too,” Renji advised.

At that moment, the door of the room was knocked on before opening.

“Princess Sylvie, do you have a moment to spare?”

The one who entered was the female knight under Sylvie’s command, Elena Broman. She had been standing on guard outside the room while Sylvie and Renji chatted.

“...I instructed you to wait outside the room until I left, did I not?” Sylvie asked in a scolding tone.

“Yes, but—Jean Bernard is requesting your audience.”

Elena hesitatingly uttered the name of the visitor. Jean Bernard was the alias of the Proxia Empire ambassador, Reiss, when he was acting in the Rubia Kingdom.

“My audience? Fine. I’ll return to the castle immediately. Sorry, Renji, let’s leave it at this for today—”

Sylvie was wrapping up her chat with Renji with a grimace when Elena interrupted her to stop her. “Princess. Regarding that... Jean Bernard has actually come here...”

“Here? Ngh, how did he know...?” Sylvie’s expression grew even more bitter.

Does he know about Renji? He’s a famous adventurer, so it wouldn’t be odd if he did... What does he want? All kinds of possibilities came to mind.

Renji saw the look on Sylvie’s face and tilted his head in suspicion. Just then, the aforementioned Jean Bernard—otherwise known as Reiss—appeared beside Elena before the door.

“Pardon my sudden intrusion.” Reiss placed a hand against his chest and bowed his head respectfully at Sylvie and Renji.

I haven’t seen this face before... Haven’t heard his name before, either. Isn’t it rude for a mere retainer to visit a princess undercover without any warning? Renji thought such things as he watched Reiss carefully.

“...What do you want?” Sylvie asked in a displeased tone.

“I heard that you were here, so I came to visit. Before I state my business, may I first give Sir Renji the Aloof my greetings?” Reiss stared at Renji with a cheerful grin that bordered on creepy.

“Well, I don’t mind. But you’re taking up my private time right now. Your business better be important.” Renji leaned back on the sofa, crossing his legs as he spoke menacingly.

“Yes, it most likely is. Then, if I may give a short greeting: I am Jean Bernard, an unworthy Rubian noble of the lowest rank.”

“I’ve never heard of your name or family.” Renji had no interest in the nobility of the Rubia Kingdom, so that was a given. A normal noble would have felt offended by Renji’s words at this point, but—

“Indeed, as we are on the very bottom rung of the social ladder. It is a great honor to meet the renowned Aloof one.” Reiss avoided the topic with a truly pleasant smile.

“...” Renji watched Reiss with narrowed eyes.

What a creepy dude. The grim look on Sylvie’s face is bothering me, too.

He tried to look out for any changes in expression, but it was like the man was wearing a mask. There was something strange about him.

“Hey. What is the meaning of this, Bernard?” Sylvie interrupted in an aggravated tone.

“I had something to discuss with Your Highness regarding the adorable, adorable Princess Estelle. Isn’t it time you went to see her?”

“...What do you mean?”

“I mean exactly what I just said...” Reiss cocked his head calmly.

“...I can see her?”

“Yes. That was our previous agreement, was it not? That you would eventually see her again. However, I am rather busy myself and would be inconvenienced if anything strange got in the way, so if you want to see her, now would be the best time.”

“...Fine.” After hesitating for a long moment, Sylvie nodded.

“What’s going on, Sylvie? Wasn’t Estelle recuperating?” Renji asked dubiously.

“I’m going to where she’s resting. Sorry, but I’ll be leaving for today. I’ll visit you again some time, Renji.” Sylvie put on an air of composure with a fleeting smile and stood up.

“Right, that’s fine...” Renji stared at Sylvie, not entirely convinced. However, she was already halfway out the door before he could do anything about it.

“Lead the way then, Bernard,” she said to Reiss.

“As you wish, Your Highness.”

Reiss pasted a grin on his face and turned to head out of the room and down the corridor. Sylvie followed him out. Just before Reiss left, he gave Renji a look. He flashed a suggestively suspicious smile before vanishing outside the door.

The way Sylvie was acting... Is something strange happening? That man is definitely suspicious...

Renji’s instincts felt heightened. Reiss’s suspicious grin flashed in his mind, giving him an uneasy feeling as he looked out the window at the inn entrance below. Reiss and Sylvie were both boarding a horse carriage. There was something menacing about the two of them.

Weird. Should I follow them and investigate?

With that decided, Renji quickly prepared his belongings and stepped out of the inn.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, inside the carriage Sylvie and Elena were riding on...

There was no telling how long it had been since they set off. A suffocating silence continued inside the carriage.

“Hey, Reiss. Who is this man?” Sylvie asked for the identity of the third party sitting diagonally across from her in the cramped carriage. The man’s left eye was hidden behind a jet-black eyepatch, his left arm wrapped in bandages with some kind of spell formula written on them. There was an alarming aura of bloodlust emanating from him.

“He’s my guard, as it would be unnerving for someone as powerless as me to travel alone. His name is Lucius. He’s in a bit of an irritated mood at the moment, so don’t try anything strange. I cannot guarantee your life if you do,” Reiss answered with a refreshed look, shrugging his shoulders.

“Lucius?”

“Oh, do you know of him?”

“If it’s the commander of the Heavenly Lions, then I’ve heard of the name. However, I don’t recall doing anything that would warrant this amount of bloodlust directed at me. It makes me want to cut him down before I’m attacked first,” Sylvie said, glaring intensely at Lucius.

“Ha!” Lucius suddenly let out a burst of delighted laughter.

“What?” Sylvie furrowed her brows.

“This bloodlust isn’t directed at you, y’know? The bastard I’m dying to kill is somewhere else. In fact, I’d like nothing more than to go and kill him right this moment,” Lucius said with vacant, dark eyes.

“Hey, Reiss. Is this man deranged or something?” Sylvie narrowed her eyes in suspicion and questioned Reiss. But Reiss merely gave a light shrug without answering.

“Say, Princess.”

“...” Lucius had addressed her, but Sylvie adamantly ignored him.

“Imagine this. Your sister—Estelle, was it? A woman that beautiful was taken hostage. Do you really think she’s still safe right now?”

“Y-You!” Sylvie reacted fiercely when her little sister’s safety was brought up, a vein standing out on her forehead.

“Heh.” Lucius sneered.

“Was that statement just now a declaration that you don’t treat hostages as hostages? If so, this ends here,” Sylvie reached for the sheath at her waist.

“Hey now, do you plan on drawing that thing in such a tight space?” Contrary to his words, the smirk on Lucius’s face was eager for her to do just that.

“Do you think I am incapable of cutting through you and the iron plate of this carriage at the same time?” Sylvie snapped.

A tense atmosphere filled the carriage. Beside Sylvie, Elena also switched to prepare for battle with a grim expression. She was braced to act if something happened.

Lucius reclined back arrogantly, continuing to provoke them with his gaze. At this rate, one would expect a fight to break out at any moment, but Reiss intervened with a fed-up expression. “Stop that. We are acting formally on behalf of our nation. We’re not the same as your average bandit or mercenary, so we wouldn’t do anything to harm the hostage we obtained. Princess Estelle is completely unharmed,” Reiss said to Sylvie.

“Acting formally for your nation? You mean the nation that rose from mercenaries?” Sylvie was seething with anger, frowning as she refuted him.

“How strange. It’s because you consider us a formal nation that you’ve agreed to this secret alliance, no?”

“Shameless words for one who took Estelle as hostage before forcing negotiations...”

“That’s another strange statement. Hostages have been used in cross-national negotiations since ancient times, no? Even for internal politics, it wasn’t rare for lords to seek hostages from their retainers as an assurance of obedience...” Reiss tilted his head curiously.

“Don’t think a nation that takes hostages will be truly trusted in an alliance.”

“I shall keep it in mind. However, a pact is a pact. We will endeavor in matters other than the hostage in order to form a trustworthy relationship. Therefore, your side should also bear in mind not to ruin a relationship of mutual trust. Well, a few complaints here and there can be overlooked,” Reiss replied calmly to the glare Sylvie sent him.

“...”

Sylvie snorted softly and refrained from speaking further. Though reluctant, that was a silent sign of agreement to Reiss’s words. Several minutes later, the carriage came to a stop.

“Shall we leave the carriage now?” Reiss suggested. Sylvie and Elena got down first, with Reiss and Lucius following them.

So we’ve been brought out of the capital after all, huh?

In order to check on Estelle’s safety, before boarding the carriage, she had agreed to the condition that the destination wouldn’t be revealed until arrival. The window had been closed while they’d traveled, so she didn’t know what route they had taken either, but she had a faint suspicion that they were heading outside the capital. The capital of the Rubia Kingdom was Sylvie’s territory, and Reiss wasn’t senile enough to let her reunite with Estelle in such a place.

Sure enough, their current location was along the road stretching from the capital, far enough for the tallest royal castle in the capital to be seen in the distance.

“I don’t see Estelle.” Sylvie looked around. There was no sign of anyone on the road besides them, and they were surrounded by uninhabited grass plains on either side of the road. It seemed the grass lacked nutrition, as the color was poor and the length short. There were boulders large enough to hide a person scattered about the place.

“Please, come this way.” Reiss gestured with his hand and invited her off the road. Leaving the carriage and driver on the road, he led the way forward.

“Princess Sylvie, I shall be behind you.”

“Right.”

Sylvie first followed Reiss, with Elena walking behind her. Further behind her was Lucius, and the four of them proceeded in a single line. Sylvie warily watched Reiss before her, while Elena warily watched Lucius in the rear as they walked.

“You informed your other subordinates that you would be heading out with me when we departed from the inn, so there’s no need to be so wary. As long as you don’t try anything yourself, that is.” Reiss chuckled as he spoke to the two walking behind him.

“I don’t intend on doing anything as long as I can confirm Estelle’s safety. However, I hope you’re ready for the worst if I find Estelle has been harmed.”

“In that case, neither of us have anything to worry about. Please stop here,” Reiss said, pointing to a large boulder ahead him. Three hooded men and a girl appeared from behind that boulder. It seemed she was wearing a magic-sealing collar, but there was no sign of any injuries. She had a sad look in her eyes, seeing her older sister a hundred meters before her.

“Estelle!” Sylvie reflexively burst into a run. However—

“Ah ah, please do not get any closer than this.” Reiss stood in her way.

“Ngh...”

“As promised, you’ve confirmed her safety. It’s about time we turned back,” Reiss said ruthlessly, his expression cool. Sylvie sent a murderous glare towards him.

“What?! I’ve only seen her face! And from this far!”

“But you’ve seen her, no? You’ve achieved the goal of confirming her safety.”

“As if I can be sure she’s unharmed with just a look. At least let me speak to her,” Sylvie pleaded desperately.

“We would be accepting a rather high risk if I allowed that... But fine. One of the reasons why this meeting was arranged was to make sure your stress didn’t prompt you to act out of line,” Reiss said, placing his hand by his mouth in a thinking manner.

“Then...”

“However, there is one condition you must accept. If you accept that condition, I will allow you to have an uninterrupted conversation for several seconds.”

“Let’s hear it.” Even if it was only for a few short moments, the thought of being able to converse with Estelle was enticing enough for Sylvie to at least listen to the condition.

“Your Highness must hand that enchanted sword over to your guard knight.”

“...Is that all?” Sylvie asked in surprise. She expected a more demanding condition from Reiss at such an opportune moment.

The enchanted sword Sylvie used was also a national treasure of an ancient artifact. She wouldn’t have let Reiss or Lucius hold it, and even in comparison to those untrustworthy alliance partners, she could just barely entrust it to her close aide Elena.

“Yes. For someone as powerful as the Princess Knight, I would have preferred to place magic-sealing shackles on you, but I shall put my trust in you. Think of this as an act of deepening our trust in each other,” Reiss requested in an oddly serious tone for once.

“Fine... Elena, please hold on to this for a short moment.” Sylvie detached the sheath at her waist and handed it to Elena.

“I shall handle it with the greatest care.” Elena knelt and accepted the enchanted sword reverently.

“Go ahead, then,” Reiss prompted.

Sylvie walked towards Estelle. Estelle herself had been temporarily freed and began moving towards Sylvie timidly. The closer the two of them got to each other, the faster their feet moved.

“Are you unharmed, Estelle?”

“Yes. I’m so sorry for all the trouble I’ve caused, Sylvie.”

The two of them linked their hands and exchanged words of reunion. Sylvie was smiling in joy from seeing her little sister safe, but Estelle’s expression was gloomy due to the fact that her own existence was now an inconvenience to her sister and her kingdom.

“Don’t let it bother you—you’re not at fault here. Don’t be rash and do anything odd.” Sylvie gripped Estelle’s hand tightly.

“Okay...” Estelle nodded with a flash of an admirable smile.

“Have they done anything strange to you?”

“Nothing in particular. I’ve been placed in confinement, but my living conditions aren’t that different to staying in the castle.”

“I see... Is there anything else troubling you?”

“Nothing. I’m sure you’re far worse off than I am. If the necessity arises, please discard me.”

“Such a necessity will never arise. Never,” Sylvie stated, her expression strained.

“Thank you...” Estelle placed her hands on her chest and bowed her head with a fleeting smile.

“Time’s up.” Reiss approached Sylvie from behind, accompanied by Elena and Lucius.

“All right.” Sylvie turned with a sigh and approached Elena, who stood beside Reiss.

“Take this, Your Highness.”

“Right.”

Elena kneeled on the ground, returning the enchanted sword to Sylvie. While doing so, she got a good look at Estelle’s unharmed figure and let out a small sigh of relief.

“Now, Princess Estelle. Please return to those men,” Reiss said, looking at the three hooded men by the boulder.

“Okay.” Estelle nodded. She separated herself from Sylvie and the others and started walking back.

Then, from a boulder located diagonally beside Estelle and the men, a figure leaped out at superhuman speed. The figure dashed to cut into the space between Estelle and her captors, and there was a silhouette of a halberd-like weapon in their hand. The mysterious figure raised their long weapon easily in a single hand, blocking the way of the men and slamming the weapon down into the ground.

“Wha...?!”

A giant wall of ice appeared between Estelle and the hooded men. It was several meters tall and had appeared right before Estelle, making her shrink in on herself. Sylvie and Elena looked shocked. But on the other hand...

Hehe. Like the rumors said, he seems to be a boy of decisive character. Thanks to that, I’ve been saved the trouble of pointing out where he was hiding myself.

Reiss grinned eerily as he watched the back of the figure standing before Estelle.

◇　◇　◇

A mysterious figure suddenly stood between the three hooded men and Estelle, forming an ice wall to divide them.

“R-Renji?!”

The hero who could control the divine arms Cocytus: Kikuchi Renji.

“Oh? What is the meaning of this, Princess Sylvie?” Reiss twisted his mouth with a chuckle and immediately questioned Sylvie beside him.

“N-No, this is...” Sylvie was in a panic, thinking he had followed them from the inn, when—

“I should be saying that.” Renji carried his halberd against his shoulder as he approached. Then, he stood as though to protect Estelle from Reiss and the others.

“Renji...” Estelle blinked and stared at him.

“Why, if it isn’t Sir Renji the Aloof. We just met earlier. Then, I shall ask you instead: what is the meaning of this?” Reiss asked with a fearless smile.

“Did you not hear me? I should be the one asking that. Sylvie said Estelle was recuperating. Why is she being treated as though she’s your hostage? Let’s hear what you have to say about that.”

Renji frowned, glaring back at Reiss.

“Why, that would be because she is a hostage,” Reiss acknowledged without a hint of guilt.

“Oh? So you’re not even gonna make any excuses? You have some nerve.”

“That’s because I have no need to make any excuses in the first place. You’re the one who’s interrupting us with no awareness of what’s going on, trying to take control as though you own the situation. Aren’t you the one with some nerve here?”

“My understanding of the situation is fine. No matter how I look at it, you’re using Estelle as a hostage to control Sylvie. That’s what you acknowledged yourself,” Renji scowled as he argued back.

“Indeed. You’ve happened across a scene of hostage diplomacy.”

“What trash... Sylvie, Elena, come over here. Estelle is secure now, so there’s no reason to obey them anymore.” Renji glared at Reiss with contempt in his gaze.

“Are you sure about that?” Reiss chuckled smugly.

“I’m not asking you.”

“I see. But did you think we would overlook that passively?” Reiss asked.

The three hooded men appeared from both sides of the ice wall Renji had created; they had their swords drawn and held at the ready.

I made the wall with the intention of trapping them inside, but I guess they evaded at the last moment, huh? It seems they’re fairly agile. That aside, why do Sylvie and Elena look so scared? Renji observed those around him quickly. “If you don’t want to make an enemy of me, the one they call Aloof and the Ice Emperor, you should retreat. I don’t know who you are or where you’re from, but you don’t want to die in a place like this, do you?” he said to Reiss, who stood in his line of fire.

“What a cheap provocation.”

“I don’t recall provoking anyone.”

“I see. A natural airhead, are you?”

“Fine, it seems you want to make an enemy of me...” To intimidate Reiss, Renji made a show of looking at his halberd and holding it ready.

“I see, I see. It seems you’re even more egoistic than the rumors make of you. Reckless, hasty, and arrogant. The type of personality unsuitable for negotiating, yet you seem to have a fair talent for it.” Without any particular sign of shrinking back, Reiss applauded Renji with an unconcerned look.

“Are you looking down on me?”

“I’m praising you. The way you flash your tremendous might to one-sidedly have your way is exactly that of a major nation dealing with a minor nation. The courage you have in forcing things to go your way is truly splendid.”

“He’s just an idiot with no knowledge of how the world works, you mean?” Lucius interrupted with a mocking laugh.

“Sounds like that man wants to die first.”

Renji lifted his halberd up with one hand, pointing the tip at Lucius.

“Hey, Reiss. Can I kill this impudent brat?” Lucius asked.

Reiss chuckled. “Has your interest finally been piqued?”

“...Did you just call me a brat?” Renji frowned in displeasure. There were less people who looked down on him by calling him short or bratty nowadays, but that kind of thing had happened regularly back when he first became an adventurer. Thus, for Renji, scornful words like “brat” were taboo. He had taught everyone who had looked down on him like that a painful lesson, without exception.

“I have no idea who you think you are, but no matter how I look at it, you’re a brat. Especially the part where you overestimate yourself just because you’ve gained a little face as an adventurer.” Lucius sneered at Renji with contempt.

“I’ve taught all the people who’ve looked down on my appearance a lesson. You may end up in the same boat.”

“So you were looked down on for both your appearance and your attitude. How scary. Sorry about that, little egoistical one.”

“You just keep talking...” Renji was seething with enough anger to attack at any moment, glaring at Lucius with dangerous eyes.

“W-Wait, Renji. Don’t be rash,” Sylvie called out to him in a hurry.

“...What are you saying, Sylvie? These people took Estelle hostage so you couldn’t oppose them, right?” Renji asked in confusion.

“That’s...” Sylvie fell silent with a conflicted expression.

It’s true that this situation may seem favorable. However, the Rubia Kingdom as it is now doesn’t have enough power to oppose the Proxia Empire. If I go with the flow of things and take Renji’s side, the Proxia Empire may earnestly begin to invade us as retaliation. If that happens, our kingdom will fall in a matter of months. If the fact I assisted the Proxia Empire at the last banquet circulates, we could be isolated from the nations around us. It would be different if the rescue was done in secret, but this situation is...

It was possible she was overthinking it, but what if this situation was a trap by Reiss? Her attention had been completely focused on her reunion with Estelle, but when she looked back upon it now, she had plenty of reason to fear that the conversation in the inn was made to entice Renji into following them.

If so, this situation could have been set up by Reiss in order to ascertain Sylvie’s true intentions. That was the natural assumption to make. Despite still being shaken by this situation, Sylvie desperately racked her brain.

“What’s wrong? Please say something, Sylvie,” Renji called out, slightly anxious.

“Hehe. It seems our relationship is already strong enough to withstand something as simple as transferring the hostage,” Reiss answered on Sylvie’s behalf.

“What...?” Renji frowned. He could already imagine that it was because they were threatening her with another reason.

“Renji. I appreciate the sentiment behind you acting for my sake, but this is our kingdom’s problem. It’s not something that can be solved by me returning to the kingdom at this point.”

Estelle, who had been silent beside Renji until now, finally made up her mind and spoke up. Her expression and words were both gentle, but at the same time had a hint of resignation.

“See? This is why I called you reckless, hasty, and arrogant. You’ve stepped into a matter that can’t be solved with your power,” Reiss sneered.

“I said it too. That you’re an idiot who doesn’t understand the way the world works,” Lucius taunted Renji with a hearty laugh.

“...” Renji stood where he was, trembling with fury. After making such a dramatic declaration of his intent to rescue her, the hostage herself had refused to be saved. It must have been a comical sight indeed.

“...Don’t look down on me,” Renji muttered after a moment.

“Ah?” Lucius replied without any interest left.

“Do you really think my power can’t solve this?” Renji asked Reiss and Lucius with a glint of anger that had nowhere to go in his eye.

“Bwahaha, you really are a brat after all. Why don’t you switch from an adventurer to a trainee clown?” Lucius said while holding back his laughter.

“I’ll say this one more time: don’t look down on me.”

“What if I do?”

“You have two options: rub your head against the ground and apologize to me through the blood running down your forehead, swearing to keep away from Sylvie and Estelle, or be killed by me right here. Well? You decide.”

“I believe there are many more options available than that, though.”

“Oh?”

The tension between Lucius and Renji was like treading on ice.

“H-Hey. Stop, Renji! Don’t do anything foolish!” Sylvie tried to stop him in a hurry, but—

“Sorry, but this isn’t your problem anymore. It’s my problem now. I can’t forgive anyone who looks down on me. I have to settle this in my adventurer way—especially against Mr. Eyepatch over there. Are you ready?”

Being looked down upon was defeat. That was what being an adventurer was about, which was why he refused to listen any longer. His head was filled with nothing but rage towards Lucius and Reiss now.

“Well, I never intended on letting you go home quietly now that you’ve witnessed this scene anyway. Which means...” Reiss made a show of looking at Lucius, who was accompanying him as a guard. Lucius gave a light shrug before placing his hand on the pommel of the sword sheathed at his waist.

“Please wait, Reiss! I’ll talk things out with Renji myself.” Sylvie tried to settle things peacefully.

“...Do you think I’ll lose to these guys, Sylvie?” Renji asked bitterly.

“I know plenty well that you’re an undefeated adventurer here. However, even if you do kill them, it would be a problem for us as well. Please understand,” Sylvie pleaded.

“That’s amazing. Undefeated at home, huh?”

“Please don’t provoke Renji!” Sylvie scolded Lucius for his mocking.

“You say that, but he’s already raring to go.”

“Yeah, I don’t follow anyone’s orders,” Renji declared with energy.

“Ngh...” Sylvie fretted.

“Hmm. It seems that Princess Sylvie has a fairly high opinion of Aloof’s abilities. Which makes this the perfect opportunity for us to demonstrate our abilities as cooperative partners. And so, if I may make a suggestion—how about a bet?” Reiss said as though he had just come up with an idea.

“A bet?” Sylvie frowned, wondering what he was going on about in a situation like this.

“It shouldn’t be a bad deal for you, Princess Sylvie. We’ll have a one-on-one duel between my guard Lucius and Aloof over there, and the loser has to accept the victor’s conditions. Let’s see... if the Aloof one wins, I promise to release Princess Estelle unconditionally. I will overlook his intervention here.”

“Why are you bringing this up all of a sudden...?” Sylvie asked with a wary look.

“Why, you ask? Because I highly value the fact you didn’t betray us when the Aloof one first intervened. As proof that it’s greatly contributed to our trusting relationship, I just wanted to prepare something befitting.”

“In that case, I shall do the fighting—”

“No, it’s going to be me.” Renji spoke over Sylvie’s objections to the duel.

“Renji...”

“Like I said, this is my fight now. I have no intention of backing down after being made a fool of to this extent.”

“Then it’s decided.” Reiss smiled pleasantly.

“I have no objections to the bet, but the fight is mine. I want an additional condition.”

“As you wish.” Reiss agreed easily to Renji adding a condition. Sylvie’s face twisted bitterly.

“Hmph. But before I state my condition, let me hear your condition on the off chance that Mr. Eyepatch wins,” Renji said.

“I have only one request if Lucius wins: that from then onwards, you will become my subordinate and follow my orders. For example, if I tell you to fight someone I designate,” Reiss explained.

“...Fine. In return, if Mr. Eyepatch loses to me, you’re going to give me all your money and become my slaves.”

“Hehehe, very well. Then it’s decided. If you have anything you want to say before the duel, go ahead. You may temporarily keep Princess Estelle over with you as well.” It was clear the contents of Renji’s conditions were harsher than Reiss’s, but Reiss agreed readily with a fearless smile. Then, he started walking out of earshot of Sylvie’s conversation and towards Lucius.

“...Hey, Reiss,” Lucius said to Reiss’s back in a displeased tone.

“Oh? Are you doubting your ability to win?”

“That’s not it.”

“Rest assured. Even if you win, I wouldn’t do anything like use the Aloof one to pour water over your thirst for revenge. I’ll be disappointed if you lose, so I intend on giving you extensive backup,” Reiss added with a shrug, sensing that Lucius was dissatisfied.

“I’m saying I don’t need that backup.”

Perhaps it was because they were talking about Rio now, but Lucius’s atmosphere had completely changed. His voice took on an ice-cold tone with not a drop of warmth whatsoever.

“Oh? But that eye and arm of yours are products of my most dedicated form of backup, no? Are you saying you’ll carry out your revenge without using them?”

“...Silence.” Lucius exuded even more anger at Reiss’s carefree attitude.

“Good grief. What a whimsical person indeed. However, you need to find the location of the boy, no? I’d appreciate it if you trusted me a little more.”

“I know you well. You have no problem lying to people’s faces—betraying people easily after gaining their trust.”

“How harsh.”

“But I don’t care what kind of man you are outside of my business with that bastard. So hurry up and tell me his location.”

“I’ve told you many times already, his location is under investigation. I haven’t been able to grasp his trail after he delivered the Beltrum Kingdom’s first princess to the Restoration. He’s the type of person to wander all over the place, after all,” Reiss said with a sigh.

“In that case, I don’t have any reason to cooperate with you,” Lucius said, implying that he was free to act independently.

“I have a plan. And my methods should be to your liking. I believe it should be far more efficient than searching on your own. It would be one matter if you accompanied me, but if you don’t accompany me then I’ll have to exclude you when I make my move, no?”

“Is that a declaration of war?”

“I’m hurt. I even prepared this fight for you as a prelude to your fight with your beloved one. You’ve been recuperating recently, so your battle senses have dulled a little, have they not?”

“...I’m losing interest in this.”

It was true that Lucius’s skills had dulled after his long recuperation period. That, and he did think crushing Renji would act as a good distraction. However, when he thought about how this development was entirely planned by Reiss, his interest was immediately dampened.

“Now, don’t say that. Please use this battle to test the abilities of that eye and arm. If you lose, we’ll become his slaves, you know,” Reiss chuckled.

“Are you saying I’ll lose?”

“Not at all. As long as he hasn’t awakened as a hero, there isn’t even the slightest chance of you losing to him.”

“Hmph. Time to finish this quickly, then. Seems like they’re ready too.” Lucius stopped in his tracks and turned as he spoke. Renji had also finished saying what he needed to say to Sylvie and the others and was watching Lucius and Reiss with a sharp gaze.

“Shall we begin, then?” Reiss and Lucius approached Renji once more.

◇　◇　◇

Renji and Lucius glared at each other as they stood on a wild grass field littered with boulders. Beside them were Reiss and Sylvie, and another few dozen meters in the distance were Estelle, Elena, and the three hooded men.

“Now, for some simple rules. A victory will be decided by making your opponent surrender or rendering them unable to fight any further. Killing is technically against the rules, but there isn’t really a penalty for doing so. Any objections?” Reiss explained briefly.

“Oh? My abilities aren’t suited for knocking enemies unconscious, but you’re saying it’s fine if I end up killing him? How convenient.” Renji smirked, his mood brightening at the opportunity to finally silence the man before him. He didn’t doubt his own ability to win at all, which strangely calmed his anger and elevated his spirits. He was undoubtedly in his best condition.

“I don’t mind if you come at me with the intention to kill me. Use that halberd’s power however you wish. Don’t hold back,” Lucius responded boldly.

“That was my intention from the start... After all your boasting, you’d better survive the first hit. I’ve grown so bored of finishing off all my enemies in one shot,” Renji lamented, sighing dramatically.

“Sure. Look forward to it.” Lucius drew the black sword at his waist with his left hand as he spoke. Then, he removed his eyepatch. Underneath was an eyeball the color of all-engulfing darkness. There was no distinction between the pupil, iris, or conjunctiva. It was as though he had pitch-black darkness in place of a left eye.

Left-handed, huh... His left arm covered in bandages also seems strangely showy... Is he afflicted by an other-world version of eighth-grader syndrome? Not to mention that black sword...and what’s with that creepy black eye? Can he even see with that?

Renji looked at Lucius in disgust.

“Hey, why are you standing still? Got cold feet?” Lucius asked with a sneer.

“No, I was looking at your left eye and arm, and that sword. They all seem oddly showy, so it’d be a real laugh if they were just for looks,” Renji chuckled mockingly.

“Cut the chit-chat there. The moment this pebble I throw hits the ground, the match will begin. Now, both of you take your places. We shall stand back as well,” Reiss said, walking over to where Estelle was with Sylvie. Once he was twenty or so meters away, he threw a rock roughly the size of his palm. The rock flew in a parabolic line, landing between Renji and Lucius. The moment it landed, Renji closed the ten meters of distance to Lucius in the blink of an eye, swinging his halberd downwards with great force.

Lucius reacted to that speed by moving backwards by a minimal distance. The blade of the ax missed Lucius’s face by a hair’s breadth.

“Hmm, so you can react properly to this speed,” Renji said as though he was impressed. “But now it’s time for you to die.” Instantly, the area ten meters before him froze over, creating a block of ice several meters tall that swallowed Lucius.

“Hmph. Looks like you were all talk after all...” Renji mumbled, venting his pent-up rage. He poured magic essence into his Divine Arms to strengthen his physical body and swung his halberd at the ice block with all his might. “Haaah!”

It was a spirited brandish. The impact caused a tremendous shattering sound, the halberd taking out a chunk of the ice without coming to a halt, sending ice powder blowing everywhere.

Renji closed his eyes and smirked, bringing his halberd up to rest on his right shoulder.

“It’s over. After all that blabbing I had to listen to, you were no different from the average punk in the adventurer’s guild... What a disappointment. It would’ve been more interesting to actually have you apologize as my slave,” he said as though assured of his victory. However—

“Indeed. Who would have imagined such a dull fool.”

The voice of someone who shouldn’t have been there could be heard. He should’ve been dead.

“Wh-What...?” Renji whipped around.

Thud. The sound of something hitting the floor.

In the next moment, Renji felt like his left side had lightened in an odd way. He turned around to see Lucius standing with his black sword in his hand.

“You’re such a disappointment, I’ve completely lost interest. This can’t even be called a warm-up to my match with that bastard,” Lucius said with a bored look.

Renji looked at Lucius with an incredulous face. Then he turned his gaze to the ground where the sound had come from. There was an arm on the ground wearing clothing that looked very familiar. What could this mean?

“...An arm? Wait... My left arm?”

Renji was extremely confused as he looked at where his left arm should have been. However, there was nothing there past his shoulder. Instead, a tremendous amount of red liquid was gushing out, flowing onto the ground.

“RENJI!”

One beat later, the scream of a familiar girl’s voice could be heard in the distance. Renji looked up to see Sylvie pale as a sheet, Reiss and the three hooded men obstructing her from running over to him.

“Hey.” Lucius grabbed Renji by the neck with his right hand, easily lifting his small body into the air.

“Gah...” Renji groaned in pain. Struggling for breath, he finally registered the reality of what was happening.

“What are you zoning out for over just one arm? Huh?”

“Gngh... Ugh...”

Lucius tightened his hold, making Renji’s face twist in pain. Losing his strength, the halberd in his hand fell to the ground with a dull thud.

“Are you frustrated? You must be. I get it. I also see that bastard’s face whenever I look at this left arm of mine. That’s why I won’t settle with just taking the bastard’s left arm. I won’t settle with gouging out his left eye. I won’t accept it if he dies with just that. That’s why I’ll take everything from him, right before his eyes. I’ll kill him half to death and drag him around, then drag around everyone precious to him and make him watch.” Lucius ranted about his grudge with bloodshot eyes, furiously agitated.

“Uhh... Ah... Ugh...” Renji’s consciousness was fading, the light in his eyes weakening by the moment.

“Seeing your face just now reminded me of the bastard again. That’s why I used you as a dry run of the real thing—so don’t think I’ll let you pass out this easily. Hey, you listening? What are you passing out for?!” Lucius yelled at Renji harshly, then threw his body into the hole gouged into the block of ice. The weakened ice crumbled and rained down on Renji from above.

“...”

There was utter silence for a few seconds, but after a moment, Renji’s halberd vanished from where it lay on the ground.

“Screw...you...!” Renji leaped out of the ice. His halberd was clenched in his right hand as he attacked Lucius, losing himself in his anger.

“Hmph.” Even though there was still space between them, Lucius swung the sword in his left hand. Renji then lost his balance and crashed to the ground.

“Guh?!” Renji tried to scramble to his feet, but he lost his balance and fell forward. He tried to stand up again, but fell once more.

It was as though he couldn’t get his footing at all. Renji’s feet had been severed at the knees.

“Take a look at your feet,” Lucius sneered.

Renji looked towards his lower body. “Wh-When did...?! Gah!”

Immediately after that, Lucius stood before him and kicked his face with all his might. Renji’s body flew several meters up into the air.

“Hey! This better not be all you’ve got!” Lucius cut beneath Renji and launched a sharp upwards kick at his falling body.

“Gngh...!” Renji’s body flew into the air once more. He could see Lucius’s figure getting farther away below him, but before he knew it, Lucius had disappeared. Or so he thought—

“Where are you looking?”

Lucius’s voice came from above his head, followed by a strong impact against his back. Lucius had landed an ax kick with all his might.

“Wha...?!”

Renji’s body accelerated downwards. He crashed into the ground, unable to brace himself for the impact. His halberd fell from his right hand once again. As his body rebounded back upwards from the impact, Lucius appeared before him.

“Yo,” he said cheerfully, grabbing Renji by the neck with his right hand. Then he tightened his grip.

“Aah...”

At that moment, fear filled Renji’s eyes for the very first time. As though to back that up, Cocytus vanished from where it lay on the ground. Lucius didn’t fail to notice that, either.

“Seems like you picked a fight against the wrong person, huh?” he said, throwing Renji’s body to the ground.

“Ugh... Urgh... I-I surren... Gah?!”

Lying with his face downwards, Renji used his right hand to desperately crawl away from Lucius as he tried to say he surrendered.

However, Lucius stomped on Renji’s back before he could.

She walked endlessly through the forest like that, step by step, proceeding with an ironlike will. However—

“Aaa!”

Tripped up by a plant, Christina lost her footing and toppled forward heavily with Flora on her back.

“Ugh, that hurts... A-Are you okay, Flora?”

She hurriedly looked towards Flora, but she showed no signs of waking up. Her breathing was rough and she was still completely limp.

I have to get up...

Christina supported her body with her dainty arms, somehow managing to get up. Her elegant dress was dampened by her sweat and absorbed the dirt from the ground, but she didn’t spare a single thought for it.

But it was difficult to use her arms at this point. While her mind could hold up, her body was screaming in protest. It was almost like she was wearing heavy weights. She was filled with the urge to fall forward on her face.

We have to leave the forest quickly. For Flora’s sake!

Christina forced strength into her arms through her sheer will. After a moment, she managed to stand up, though she was shaking like a newborn fawn.

I got up... But which way was I walking? Since I fell forward, then it was that way. But I should climb a tree to confirm our direction soon.

Perhaps she hadn’t supplied her brain with enough nutrients, as her thoughts were finally dulling. For a brief moment, she completely lost track of her thoughts and had to refocus. She was filled with uncertainty about the direction they were moving in.

They had climbed a tree to check earlier, but they definitely hadn’t done it as frequently as Rio had while they were moving from Cleia to Rodania.

What if she had made a mistake? What if they couldn’t leave the forest today because of that? What if they were attacked by beasts or monsters? Christina couldn’t even create water with magic in her current state. And even if she disregarded herself, would Flora be able to make it another night in this forest?

She was sure she had been mentally prepared to leave the forest, but that single uncertainty became the foundation for all the other worries at the back of her head to come forward.

What should I do...?

What if she couldn’t save Flora, even though she was right here beside her? Christina paled as she imagined the worst-case scenario happening.

“...I should check where we’re going.” She furiously shook her head as though to drive away her uncertainties, then voiced her current task at hand to encourage herself.

“I’m sorry, Flora. Please rest here for a while.” Christina set Flora down against a tree trunk and approached a nearby tree that looked easy to climb. Then, she slowly started scaling the tree.

The sun hadn’t set yet. Though she was worried it would be impossible to leave the forest by the end of today, she continued to climb.

Eventually, she reached the top of the tree.

I’m tired...

Christina first looked for the position of the sun. It was still bright out, but sunset would surely happen within the next few hours.

Next, she looked around at her surroundings.

The smoke is close... I can see the edge of the forest.

She spotted the smoke they were heading for as a sign of civilization. At the far depths of her view, she could see where the trees came to an end. It meant the time for them to leave the forest was finally near.

“We can leave... We can leave! It’s the end of the forest... I have to go back down,” Christina said hoarsely, swallowing her saliva. With a slight start, she started making her way back down the tree.

“Christina...”

By the time she reached the ground, Flora had woken up.

“Flora! Thank goodness, you’re awake... I saw the edge of the forest. There’s a settlement right beside it. We’ll be able to leave the forest soon,” Christina said in relief.

“R-Really? That’s great...”

“It is. Let’s go. Come on, I’ll carry you.”

“First, the cup. Procreo Aqua. Here, please drink up.”

Flora immediately took a cup out of the blanket being used to carry supplies and recited a spell to fill it with water. The cup filled with water pouring out of the small magic circle.

“...You drink first.” Christina shook her head slowly and pushed the cup back towards Flora.

“You’ve been walking this entire time, so you drink first. I’ll make more for myself.” Flora smiled weakly and took the other cup, filling it with another spell to create water.

“Thank you,” Christina said with a bow, bringing the cup to her face elegantly. However, it seemed she was severely dehydrated, as she gulped it all down at once.

“Phew... I feel like I’ve been revived,” Christina said in a daze.

“I’m glad. I think I feel a bit better now, thanks to you carrying me this whole time,” Flora said while sipping from her cup.

“Your fever seems to go up when you move your body. You still have a bit of a fever, so let me continue to carry you. If it hurts despite that, let me know.”

“Okay... Thank you very much,” Flora said apologetically. The two of them continued to rehydrate themselves for a few minutes before setting off to leave the forest.

Not long after Christina started walking, Flora fell into a deep sleep as though she had fallen unconscious again—but they were nearly out of the forest. Christina relied on that future to keep her anxiety at bay as she continued walking as calmly as she could.

Then, roughly half an hour later...

“We’re out...”

Christina finally reached the end of the forest. It felt like an eternity since the last time she had seen anything other than trees, making her stare in a daze for a moment.

The forest came to an end at a gentle hilly area with a clear view. There were buildings that looked to form a village outside of the forest. Relief and exhaustion surged within her instantly.

“It’s a village... Let’s go and see if they have a doctor.”

Christina squeezed out what energy she had left in her body to sluggishly drag her feet towards the village. However, with her accumulated fatigue and mind focused on leaving the harsh forest, Christina had forgotten an important thing—the possibility that their pursuer was hot on their tail...

“Haha. Well done. What an effort.”

There was someone in the forest watching Christina descend the hill towards the village with Flora on her back. Lucius.

While the forest was a harsh environment for the two girls raised as princesses, it was nothing but a walk in the park for Lucius. It hadn’t taken any time for him to catch up to them at all, and once he did, he observed the royal siblings in their hard struggle.

Well, they’ll definitely rest at the village in their state. I can leave this be for now and head back to Duran.

Rio had probably visited Duran by now—if so, the moment of truth was near. Lucius grinned and flung the magic artifact to set a teleport crystal’s location to the nearby hill so that he could return at any moment.

“I’ll be back for you soon, princesses. Transilio.”

With the spell for teleportation uttered, Lucius disappeared.

◇　◇　◇

Back in Paladia’s capital...

One day had passed since Rio’s contest with Duran, and it was around the same time Christina and Flora had reached the village.

Rio hadn’t taken a single step out of his inn since the day before. Since he didn’t know when Duran’s messenger would arrive, he didn’t want to be absent from the inn if at all possible.

He had taken a book out of his Time-Space Cache to read, but none of its contents had seeped into his head. He had finally gained a clue about Lucius, so his emotions seemed to be unusually agitated.

This is no good. I need to calm down...

Rio slammed his book shut and took a deep breath. Then, someone knocked on his door.

“Yes!”

Could it be? Rio leaped out of his seat with that thought, answering at a louder voice than normal. He prepared himself sufficiently to react no matter what happened, then slowly opened the door. There, he was faced with someone unexpected.

“Prince Duran...” Rio called his name in shock. He hadn’t imagined the first prince would come to this inn in person.

Furthermore, he was here without a single guard. There was no sign of anyone else in the corridor.

Did he really come without guards? Isn’t that really careless of him? Rio thought to himself, but he had heard word of the prince’s character during his investigations upon reaching this kingdom.

“Why are you so surprised?” the large man looked down at Rio and said.

“I wasn’t expecting Your Highness to visit in person... Did you need something?” Rio asked, collecting himself.

“It’s about your reward. I came to tell you his location,” Duran said as he looked around curiously at the run-down inn room.

“Where is he?” Rio asked with bated breath.

“If you follow the road west from this capital for thirty kilometers, you’ll find a large forest. Before the forest is a village—he said he’d wait for you there.”

“...In a village?”

“Your face says you’re wondering why it’s there, of all places.” Duran chuckled, seeing through Rio’s reaction.

“Would you tell me the reason?”

“There’s someone related to you in that village, apparently.”

“...What does that mean?” Rio’s expression changed with a twitch. The words caught his attention; he had a bad feeling.

“Who knows? I have no more information than that, and you’re looking rather murderous. If it bothers you that much, why don’t you hurry along?” Duran shrugged, suggesting that Rio depart.

“Excuse me, then.”

“Sure.”

Rio left the room. He originally arrived in the clothes he was wearing, so he didn’t have any belongings to take with him.

Duran was left alone in the room. But as soon as he stepped out into the corridor, he entered the room next door.

“Was that enough, Lucius? I did everything you said, but...”

“Yes. I am most grateful.” Lucius stood up.

“That aside, you’ve sure changed a lot since the last time I saw you. He must be quite the outrageous man to make you suffer to this extent...”

Duran stared at Lucius closely. His left eye was covered by an eyepatch, and his left arm was heavily wrapped in bandages. The air around him was sharper than usual, and a hint of deep hatred no regular person would ever have could be seen in his gaze.

“Unfortunately, I don’t have time to chat with you. Reiss will have realized something was off and will visit you again soon. In the meantime, I need to get ahead of the bastard so I can lie in wait. If you’re coming along, then stay silent.”

Lucius was clearly in a bad mood. Before, he would talk to Duran—his contract partner—with some level of respect, but when Rio became the topic of conversation, he instantly unraveled.

That being said, Duran had taken on a role to help him get the jump on Reiss. After Lucius had arrived first to meet Duran, Duran had fed Reiss false information about Lucius’s whereabouts the day before. By now, Reiss should be searching for Lucius, wandering around the point he was originally supposed to direct Duran to guide Rio towards.

“Very well. In return, allow me to watch your battle with him. I’ll have to decide which of the royal sisters to receive as my reward as well.”

Duran didn’t appear particularly fazed and acted as his usual self. He had requested to spectate the showdown with Rio as repayment for assisting Lucius. Since he wouldn’t have been able to outwit Reiss without Duran, Lucius reluctantly agreed.

“Hmph... Transilio.”

Thus, the two of them headed to the village where Christina and Flora were.

Chapter 7: Before the Death Battle

Immediately after Lucius teleported to Duran, Christina stepped foot into the village beside the forest with Flora—who was unconscious—on her back.

The village was extremely quiet, but she could see villagers walking around here and there. They had also noticed Christina and were staring at her closely, but there was a secluded atmosphere hanging over the village that made it difficult to call out to them.

“Umm...”

In fact, when Christina looked at them and spoke, they averted their gazes with disgusted looks. But she couldn’t afford to feel timid. Christina approached the next villager she saw; the man was in his twenties and in the middle of working beside a cabin, so he didn’t notice Christina’s approach.

“Excuse me, do you have a moment?” Christina called out to his back. The villager flinched and turned around. When he spotted Christina with Flora on her back, he clearly froze on the spot. It seemed he hadn’t expected her to talk to him, as he looked around to check there was no one else nearby before replying.

“...Uh, yeah. Who are you?”

“Is there a doctor in this village?” Christina asked politely.

“A doctor... That would be the village chief,” the man answered with a murmur.

“Could you lead me to him? My little sister was bitten by a venomous spider and has a fever,” Christina explained succinctly.

“...All right.” The man looked at their tattered dresses in suspicion, but nodded quietly before walking off. Christina chased after him. They barely exchanged any words along the way, but the man kept glancing over curiously as he led them.

I suppose this outfit does stand out.

Christina looked down at her clothes and felt awkward.

“There’s one thing I’d like to ask.”

“What is it?” The villager flinched before turning back.

“What area are we in?” Christina tried to confirm their location with a vaguely worded question.

“The area? To the west of the Paladia Kingdom, I guess...? I’ve never really left the village, so I wouldn’t know,” the man answered, tilting his head curiously at the odd question.

Christina’s face stiffened faintly before she gave an awkward response. “I see...”

Pretty far from Rodania, then. And allied to the Proxia Empire...

They had finally made it out of the forest, but their situation hadn’t gotten any better. The influence of the Beltrum Kingdom, one of the largest powers in the Strahl region, wouldn’t be of any help here—if anything, it was more likely to be a hindrance.

It isn’t a distance I can travel while carrying Flora. What should I do...?

Faced with such a harsh reality, Christina’s face stiffened further. For now, something had to be done about the poison eating away at her sister, but she didn’t have any good ideas about what to do after that.

In the end, they arrived at the village chief’s place before she could come up with a plan to return to Beltrum.

“This is the village chief’s place. I’ll go explain the situation, so you wait here for a bit.”

The villager left behind those words and entered the house alone. Christina waited before the entrance and he returned one minute later.

“The village chief will see you. Come inside.”

“Thank you. Excuse me, then.” With Flora carried on her back, Christina gave a tiny bow before entering. A middle-aged man was waiting in the living room just past the entrance.

The villager who led them here stood beside the man who appeared to be the village chief. Beside him was another man of similar age. He stared at the filthy state of their dresses curiously when they approached.

“This... Welcome, I am the chief of this village. I’ve heard the general gist of things—you’re in need of a doctor, is it?” The middle-aged man introduced himself and bowed deeply.

“Yes. My little sister was bitten by a venomous spider in the forest. Could you examine her and see if you have any antidotes to treat her?”

“That can be done, but...would you two happen to be nobility?” The village chief looked at Christina with a searching gaze. Though it was fairly dirty, the dress she wore must have made him assume that.

“Yes.” Though she was technically royalty, Christina nodded without correcting him.

“I see, so that’s how it is. Hey. I’ll handle the rest, so you two can leave.”

The village chief ordered the two young men beside him to leave, but they remained standing there, reluctant to do so. The chief glared at them impatiently. “You’re in the way. And you shouldn’t be here to witness a noblewoman’s medical examination. Leave.”

“F-Fine.” The two men exchanged looks before dragging their feet outside.

The village chief bowed his head. “I apologize for the youngsters.”

“No, I’m the one who’s sorry for causing a fuss,” Christina said, bowing in return.

“Now, let me take a look at your sister. There’s a guest room at the back of this floor, so please head over there. I’d offer to carry her myself, but I’m afraid my back isn’t what it used to be...”

The village chief urged them to move, smiling wryly at the latter half of his words. Thus, the two of them headed towards the guest room.

“By the way, may I ask what two nobles were doing in the forest? You appear to be alone, too...” the chief asked along the way.

“We were traveling on board our transport vehicle when we were attacked by bandits. My sister and I escaped with our lives by running into the forest, but...” Christina answered tactfully.

“Oh, my... How awful that must have been for you. Wouldn’t there be quite a commotion over your disappearance by now, then?” the chief asked worriedly, as though he believed her story just now. They were the words of a noble—as long as there were no clear contradictions or suspicious factors, they wouldn’t be suspected. Though the collar around Christina’s neck was a little curious...

“Yes, most likely.”

“Considering the state of your little sister, you should stay here for the night. It may not suit the taste of nobility, but we have warm food here as well.”

“Thank you very much.”

They arrived at the guest room, and the village chief invited them inside. “Now, come in. Lay her down over there.” Christina moved beside the bed and set Flora down gently.

“...Flora?”

Flora hazily regained her consciousness and opened her eyes.

“The village doctor is taking a look at you.” Christina smiled gently to reassure her.

Flora spotted the village chief standing to the side. “Thank you very much...” she said weakly.

The doctor shook his head and began his examination. “No need to thank me. Now, where were you bitten by the spider? Please tell me all about the situation when you were bitten, and how much time has passed since then.”

“She was bitten in the neck by the spider early in the morning. She used detoxifying magic immediately, but it didn’t seem to have any effect. We were walking all afternoon, which seemed to make the venom circulate...then she passed out with a fever,” Christina answered on Flora’s behalf.

“I see. If you would excuse me... Hmm, I see, I see.” The village chief approached Flora and moved her hair to check the affected area. He immediately spotted the swollen, bruise-like mark.

A black mark, huh? I do recall there being a venomous spider in the forest that can create this. If left untreated, the black gradually spreads until it turns into necrosis. It can be treated immediately after the bite by applying a strong alcohol, but I have no idea how to treat this once it’s progressed so far... I’ve heard that the symptoms can become contagious if aggravated, too...

The village chief stared closely at the mark on Flora’s neck. If the poison eating at Flora’s body was the contagious type, then those symptoms were extremely troubling. The thought of the poison spreading through the village was terrifying, so he wanted them to leave as soon as possible. But he hesitated to say that directly to nobility.

“Will Flora be okay?” Christina asked.

“...It doesn’t look good,” the village chief answered with a pained look.

Christina paled immediately. “Y-You can’t treat her?”

“Unfortunately, I don’t have the means to treat her. Perhaps if you had a noble physician... Also, it’s possible that these symptoms may not be poison,” the chief suggested with uncertainty.

“Not poison...?”

“I fear it may be an infectious disease. If left alone, the skin will gradually blacken and rot away. It may have been treatable immediately after the bite, but I haven’t heard of anyone recovering from these symptoms after so much time has passed. While it’s truly regrettable for me to say this...”

“That can’t be...” Christina’s face grew visibly paler by the second.

“...”

I fear the disease may spread, so could you leave the village? Those words were on the tip of his tongue, but the village chief swallowed them in front of the nobles.

“Will Flora... die?” Christina asked with bated breath.

“I am not sure. I’ve heard that necrosis spreads rapidly...and since it’s on her neck, it could be bad. There’s also the fear of the disease spreading, so it may be best not to get too close...”

“Wha...”

Don’t get close? There was no way she could do that. Christina almost wanted to argue back angrily, but she could sense that the chief was troubled by Flora’s presence as a source of disease and swallowed her words.

Suddenly, the two men who had left earlier reappeared. They must have ran here, as they were panting for breath. “D-Dad! There’s big news!” they said from the other side of the open door.

“Wh-What is it?” the chief asked in confusion, seeing the serious atmosphere.

“Some important person from the kingdom has come to the village!”

“What did you say...?” The village chief slowly turned his head to look at Christina and Flora.

Did they come in search of us? If so, that means the Paladia Kingdom is involved in this incident as well...

Christina immediately processed her thoughts, but she lacked the information to make any conclusions.

“Do you have someone in mind?”

“I have no idea...” Christina shook her head nervously.

“Yo.”

“We’re coming in.”

Two new men appeared in the doorway. It was Lucius and Duran.

“Wha—?! Ngh...” Christina shot to her feet and braced herself on reflex. However, she was belatedly reminded of the fact her magic had been sealed by the collar around her neck.

Duran’s eyes widened in interest. “Ooh. What a fiery spirit we have here.”

“This is the older sister, Christina Beltrum,” Lucius informed him. The two of them marched into the room without reserve.

“Then the one lying down must be the little sister, Flora Beltrum. Hmm, she seems to be in a pinch beyond help...” Duran’s gaze turned to Flora, lying down on the bed.

“Haha! Must’ve been poisoned by some annoying creature of the forest.” Lucius laughed heartily, making an eerily accurate guess at the situation.

“Is that true?”

“...” Christina held her silence at Duran’s question.

“Hey, chief. How about it?” Lucius asked.

Overwhelmed by the atmosphere in the room, the village chief gave his answer in trembling fear. “Y-Yes, sir! She was apparently bitten by a spider in the forest! I’ve just informed them that it cannot be treated here...”

“I see... Heh, this is why you should’ve just waited quietly at the cabin. Now you’ve gone through all this effort to leave the forest before being found anyway. A wasted effort, if you will,” Lucius said mockingly.

“Ngh...” Christina bit down on her lip and clenched her fists.

She couldn’t deny that. If they had chosen to wait in the forest cabin, Flora wouldn’t have been bitten by the spider. That was the thought in her mind, but—

“I-It wasn’t wasted. It was my fault. I slowed Christina down...” Flora joined the conversation from where she lay on the bed, protecting her older sister.

“Oh, you’re awake.” Lucius looked at the bed.

“Your voice...is familiar,” Flora said weakly.

“I’m honored you remember. It’s my first time meeting the first princess, though. Good day—I’m Lucius Orgueil.” Lucius introduced himself in a pompous tone and grinned.

“Y-You’re the one who tried to kidnap Flora in Amande...” Christina’s gaze sharpened.

“Yeah, but I was interrupted by that bastard.” Lucius was reminded of that time and lowered his voice in irritation.

Duran patted Lucius’s shoulder to calm him before looking at Flora. “Save that anger for when he arrives. More importantly, we might be able to treat the second princess at the Paladia Castle.”

“What...?” Christina’s heart swayed. Her precious little sister could be saved.

“The price will be one night in bed with the first princess. How about it?” Duran added.

“Wh... Y-You wretch!” Christina glared at Duran, red in the face.

“Ha! Although, the pathetic sight of her filthy dress has made me lose my appetite. Who would imagine the princess of a major kingdom falling this far? She looks worse than a harlot from the outskirts. Nay, I can only see her as a beggar,” Duran ridiculed.

“...”

What a rude and unrefined man this was—Christina had never been so disgraced since she was born.

“Hehehe. A princess of an enemy nation. And a strong-willed one, too. Mm, what a wonderful woman indeed.” Duran laughed mockingly, but Christina had no idea if she was being praised or insulted.

“...What’s going on here?”

Just at that moment, Rio was suddenly standing before the door, looking around at the inside of the room. Christina, Flora, Lucius, and Duran were present. What kind of combination was this? He questioned the situation with a stern and doubtful face.

“S-Sir Amakawa?! Why are you here...?” Christina was shocked, her mouth falling open in a daze.

“Well, this is a surprise. How did you arrive already? There’s at least thirty kilometers from the capital to this village.” Duran stared closely at Rio. Only ten minutes had passed since he teleported here, so how was Rio here already? But Rio had flown at full speed after leaving the Paladia capital.

“There’s nothing to be shocked about. This guy can move at monstrous speeds.” Lucius glared at Rio.

“What’s the meaning of this?” Rio’s gaze sharpened, but Lucius drew his sword and pointed the tip at Flora’s throat.

“Wha...” Facing upwards where she lay on the bed, Flora stiffened faintly.

Rio also braced himself to fight at any moment.

“Whoa, there. Do you intend on fighting here?” Lucius said, looking at the dangerous air around Rio, who was ready to draw his sword.

“You were the one who drew first, no?”

“Now now, there’s no need to rush. I’ve wanted to kill you with every fiber of my being since the last time we met—I feel the same way as you.”

Without looking away from Rio for a moment, Lucius sunk the tip of his sword into Flora’s neck by a mere millimeter.

“...” Rio didn’t seem to want Flora hurt, as he frowned while subduing his bloodlust.

“Ha. That’s more like it. We can’t even swing our swords fully in this cramped place. Let’s move the slaughter outdoors.”

“...Fine.” Rio agreed to Lucius’s proposal.

“Prince Duran. Could you carry Princess Flora?” Lucius asked Duran, but Duran shot Flora a single glance before refusing point-blank.

“I refuse. She’s filthy and she reeks. I have no interest in holding such women.”

“...” Both Flora and Christina trembled with flushed faces.

“Hah, fair point. Hey, first princess. You carry your sister.” Lucius gave the order to Christina instead. The entire party then left the village chief’s house together. Curious onlookers had gathered around the chief’s house, watching them leave the house with a heavy air.

“Get lost. This isn’t a show.” Duran threatened the villagers in a sullen mood and they scattered in every direction. For some reason, the village chief and the two villagers with him had followed them, so Duran turned to them as well.

“There’s no need for you all to come along either. You’re in the way.”

The three men nodded and retreated back into the house. After that, Rio, Duran, Christina, Flora, and Lucius left the village, walking in that order.

“Princess Christina and Princess Flora should be separate from our confrontation,” Rio said to Lucius as they walked.

“That’s not quite right—they’re functioning perfectly well as hostages right now, are they not? You fought at Amande for the second princess’s sake as well. Anyways, Reiss is after these two for some reason or another. Though he has been continuously thwarted by you.” Lucius chuckled coldly, thrusting his sword at Christina’s neck.

“...” Christina broke out in a nervous sweat at the prickle of danger she could feel on her neck. Like Lucius said: no matter how she looked at it right now, they were the shackles holding Rio down. She felt terrible because of that.

“Anyway, he has a rather curious connection to you two royal sisters. I was interested in that as well, so I decided on choosing you two as hostages,” Lucius added smoothly.

“What are you saying...?” Rio frowned.

“Oh, I just found your suffering to be similar to your father’s. You have no obligation to save these two, yet here you are. Haven’t they repaid enough of your good with evil?” Lucius asked, hinting at something.

Christina and Flora held their breaths as they listened.

“So? What about it?”

“That’s not something to be dismissed, is it? I’m talking about the reason why an orphan from the slums left the Beltrum Royal Academy and went across the border, changing his name to Haruto. Ring any bells to you, Rio?”

“...And I’m asking: what about it?”

His identity had been revealed past the point of hiding anything from Christina and Flora, but Rio’s expression didn’t waver at all—he was fully aware that Lucius was trying to provoke him. However, Christina and Flora didn’t look good. Lucius purposefully made his way beside Christina to peer at their faces.

“Haha! The princesses look more upset than you. Hey, princesses. Does the name ‘Rio’ sound familiar to you? The boy you looked down upon, charged for a groundless crime, then banished grew up into this guy here. Aren’t you curious about his past? Don’t you have anything you want to say?” Lucius could see through Christina and Flora’s state of mind and chose words to incite their sense of guilt. Their expressions grew stiffer and stiffer.

“As usual, you’re even nastier than me.” Duran sighed, shaking his head.

“Watch it, Rio. Your murderous aura is scaring the princesses,” Lucius jeered at Rio’s back.

“...” Rio continued ignoring him.

“Listen up, princesses. His parents used to be from the Yagumo region. Because of some unavoidable circumstances, they migrated to the Strahl region, and the place they chose to settle down just so happened to be the Beltrum capital,” Lucius continued by himself, exposing Rio’s past to Christina and Flora.

“His father, Zen... He was a real capable one. He used his skills to distinguish himself as an adventurer, which was how he caught my eye back when I still lived in Beltrum’s capital. I managed to win over his trust after that, but what surprised me the most was the fact that Rio’s mother was a royal with a sheltered upbringing. Apparently, Zen was Ayame’s personal guard.”

Rio’s mother was royalty. This fact made Christina’s poker face crumble, her gaze trembling in shock.

“You could compare it to a princess of your kingdom marrying a knight. They both migrated since some problems happened, but that bastard, Zen, was living a happy life. Ayame was head over heels for him, and they both adored Rio. The picture-perfect family, if you will. I socialized with the family—I even played with young Rio often.”

Lucius exaggerated his emotional tone as he spoke, as though he were recalling those memories fondly. Then his mouth twisted with a smirk.

“It made me sick to my stomach, so I decided to destroy it—that happiness. I killed Zen before Rio was old enough to remember, then killed Ayame when he was five.”

“So you were the one who killed my father after all...” Rio interrupted Lucius’s monologue when he paused, speaking in a tone devoid of any warmth.

“That bastard was in such despair when he realized he was betrayed by his best friend. He made a face like the one you had when Ayame was killed right before your eyes.” Lucius could sense that Rio’s anger was slowly building and grinned crudely as he spoke.

“How awful...” Flora muttered sadly, her face flushed with her fever.

“Awful? Your kingdom did plenty of awful things to him too. He was just a brat living happily with his mother up until he was five. He may have roughened around the edges from two years struggling in the slums, but you gave him plenty of harsh treatment just because he was an orphan, no?” Lucius took this chance to prod Christina and Flora’s guilt once more.

Does this man intend to use us as hostages against Sir Amakawa? If so, why would he dig up Sir Amakawa’s past and reveal it to us like this...?

Christina sweated nervously as she tried to figure out Lucius’s intentions, but there was no way she could—the only thing she knew for sure was that she and Flora were potentially the reason why Rio was backed into a corner right now.

“What’s wrong? Cat got your tongue, princesses? I don’t know if he’ll save you, but why don’t you try begging Rio for your lives? Are you thinking of a convenient excuse for yourselves? You know he’ll probably save you even in this situation.” Lucius looked at Christina and Flora’s faces, mocking them.

“I...” Christina’s hair stood on end. Like Lucius had pointed out, part of herself felt expectant—expectant for Sir Amakawa to save them. Feeling ashamed of herself, Christina bit down on her lip. She had been so enthusiastic about protecting Flora herself, but in the end, she hadn’t been able to. Instead, she was seeking the assistance of the person she had caused so much trouble for in the past.

Even though I have no right to that...

But even if she had to sacrifice herself, she wanted to protect Flora. She had no choice but to rely on Rio for that. So, Christina tried to think of a way to give Flora the highest chance of survival. For example, if they had to be used as hostages, she needed to make sure that Rio discarded her first. And so, a pained look flashed across Christina’s face for a brief moment, before she made a curt statement.

“...That’s not true.”

“Oh? What isn’t?” Lucius asked curiously.

“It’s only natural to sacrifice the individual for the sake of the kingdom. If you wish to condemn that as an awful deed, you can condemn it all you want. I don’t recall ever doing anything awful to him—at least on an individual level, I believe. Flora may not think the same.” Christina spoke as though she were reciting a memorized speech. There was no hint of her emotions behind those words at all. However—

“Heh heh heh. How terrible. Rio was placed in an environment that could make the average person’s misfortune sound petty, you realize? He could have grown up as royalty instead. Yet through some kind of mistake, he became an orphan in the slums at the age of five. If you’re saying it’s only natural for someone like that to be used up for your political benefits, then you’re truly cold-blooded to the core.” Lucius cackled in delight, eagerly bringing up Rio’s misfortunes.

“I don’t believe you should be the one saying that, since you’re the one who made him an orphan... But you’ve made one mistake. I have no value as a hostage.” Christina looked at Lucius with clear disdain.

“Did you hear that, Rio? What do you think? Sounds real admirable, eh? She’s trying to anger you on purpose—probably so that she’ll be the first to go, right?” Lucius chuckled, seeing through her plan.

“Wha...” Christina tried to object, but she ended up biting her lip bitterly instead.

“Did you go senile walking around the forest? This bastard wouldn’t forsake you. If he was going to abandon you, he would’ve cut down my back ages ago. He’s trying to save you in this situation. The hypocrisy is disgusting,” Lucius spat.

“That’s enough. How far are we going?”

Rio called for Lucius to stop. They were currently on a hill, several hundred meters away from the edge of the village.

“Fine. Let’s settle this,” Lucius said, pointing his sword at Christina’s neck.

“Ah...” Christina swallowed her breath and froze.

“What, can’t draw your sword?” Lucius sneered.

“...” Rio glared at Lucius sharply, but didn’t draw the sword at his waist.

“Ha. If you want to win against me, you should throw away everything other than your bloodlust. You’re the same as Zen—you try to fight while carrying excess weight on you. And yet, you’re strong. That’s what I can’t stomach. Living like a walking contradiction... But that’s precisely why you’ll die unable to protect those close to you. I’ll prove it to you—the foolishness of a human carrying around that kind of unnecessary weight.” Until now, Lucius had been using an exaggerated tone to provoke Rio, but the bloodlust he had been holding back was released as he glared back at him.

“I don’t get it... What do you gain from me throwing away that so-called excess weight?” Rio asked in an indifferent tone. Lucius was obviously speaking of Christina and Flora.

“I’m saying if you don’t, you won’t be able to defeat me in this battle. Then... Was it Celia Claire? And a woman named Miharu—I’ll go after those women next. Of course, I’ll enjoy them to the fullest before killing them. Don’t worry, though. I’ll leave you half-alive and bring you along to witness it,” Lucius boasted to irritate Rio.

“...”

Perhaps it was because Celia and Miharu’s names had been mentioned, but Rio’s wrath swelled. As though to embody that rage, a tremendous amount of magic essence poured out of Rio’s body.

“Ha! You finally look like a proper avenger now.” Lucius smirked, removing his left eyepatch.

Interlude: The Fifth Hero

Several months ago, around the time Satsuki, Rui, Hiroaki, and Takahisa were summoned to the Strahl region...

In the group of small kingdoms sandwiched between the Galarc Kingdom and the Proxia Empire, there was a small country called the Vilkis Kingdom. On the eastern side of this kingdom, a hero was secretly summoned.

The hero’s name was Kikuchi Renji, a high school student who lived in Japan. He was slightly below the average height of a male high school student at 160 centimeters tall, and he had an innocent but strong-willed look on his face.

“Where...is this? Am I...standing in a crater?” Renji muttered, wide-eyed and confused.

After returning home from school, he had left the house still dressed in his uniform to drop by the convenience store. Yet before he knew it, he found himself standing in an unfamiliar place. The area where Renji stood was gouged into the ground like a round crater, leaving him in the center. It was no wonder he was surprised.

There was no sign of anything man-made around him, and it seemed whatever had created this crater had blown away everything around it during the impact—there was nothing but the ground spreading out in a circle around him wherever he looked. The edge of the crater appeared to be several hundred meters away, but Renji couldn’t tell what was going on outside the crater from where he stood.

“It’s a little cold... And today was meant to be warm... Is this still Japan?”

Renji trembled in his school blazer as he took another good look around. The time of day hadn’t changed, but the location was completely different. It was at this moment that a thought crossed his mind.

It’s almost like one of those other-world summoning novels.

Japanese people were reading a lot of novels involving summoning to another world, so the possibility occurred to him.

“Nah, that couldn’t be.”

The novels Renji read were merely a form of entertainment to kill time. Fictional worlds inside fictional stories. There was no way that could happen in real life.

“But...”

Something that should’ve been impossible had happened. He was in a situation that couldn’t be explained in any other way. Renji cast his eyes over the area and gulped.

I guess I’ll check what’s going on outside the crater.

With that decided, Renji started walking towards the edge of the crater. There was an incline from the center to the farthest edge, so moving out of the crater was easy. He arrived at the edge to see a forest of trees spread before him.

“A forest, huh...” Renji closed his eyes as though to avoid reality and tapped himself on the head a few times, then opened his eyes and looked around again. The crater was still surrounded by trees as far as he could see.

“That’s right, my smartphone...is out of range, huh?” Renji suddenly took his smartphone out of his blazer pocket. The impossible situation had shaken him so much, he forgot about the first tool he should have checked. However, the symbol near the battery indicator showed he was out of the network range. This meant that even if he was still in Japan, he wouldn’t be able to use an app to find his location.

“I guess...I’ll look around outside the crater for now.”

It was possible that this crater was located at the edge of the forest, and he’d be able to make his way out easily.

With that decided, Renji sighed heavily and started walking.

◇　◇　◇

Some time later...

“Well, that was a waste of time after all...”

Renji was unable to find a way out and sighed heavily. No matter where along the outer perimeter of the crater he stood, he couldn’t see the end of the forest.

“Do I have no choice but to enter the forest? I guess not... Hm?”

He leaned against a tree while looking around at the area and talking to himself. Then, from the other side of the crater, a group of people appeared from the forest. There were eight of them.

“That’s...!”

Renji spotted the figures opposite to his position and almost ran forward without thinking. However, he was stopped by the caution that rose within him.

No matter how you look at it, they’re not Japanese... They’re dressed like they walked straight out of a fantasy world. Some of them even have swords.

Renji quickly hid behind the tree he was leaning on and strained his eyes to watch the group that came out of the forest. They were all men in their twenties to forties. Some of them had spades in their hands. If those were farming tools, were they being used in place of weapons? They didn’t have any defensive equipment like armor, shields, or helmets equipped, and the clothes they were wearing all varied. Compared to the school uniform Renji wore, they seemed quite plain.

They don’t seem like soldiers... Are they villagers? Renji guessed.

They’re pointing at the crater and saying something.

The villagers seemed to be excited. He couldn’t tell what they were saying, but there didn’t appear to be any anger in their expressions. Were they surprised?

That aside, my eyes feel like they can see really clearly right now... They should be pretty far away, yet I can see their faces without a problem, Renji suddenly thought. His vision didn’t require glasses, but both eyes were below 1.0. He wondered why he could see so far and so clearly.

Are they coming this way?

The men started walking along the outside of the crater.

Even if I showed myself, we wouldn’t be able to communicate. I don’t want to approach armed men barehanded either. Let’s see what happens a bit longer.

Renji decided to retreat a little farther into the forest. The attention of the villagers was drawn to the crater, as though they were wary of something.

There may be wolves or other dangerous beasts. Wait, this is a fantasy world, so monsters might also be possible.

Once he reached that thought, Renji glanced back at the forest in fear. There were only dense trees growing there, but the thought of dangerous creatures gave him the chills. However, he couldn’t move from his current position. Renji hid himself in the trees and waited for the villagers to approach.

After roughly ten minutes had passed, the men were finally beside the trees Renji was hidden behind. Renji retreated a little farther into the forest to avoid detection, holding his silence while listening attentively to them.

“Chief, how do we explain this to the lord of the region?”

“No clue. We have no choice but to report the reality as is—that all the water in the lake has vanished.”

Obstructed by the trees, there was roughly ten meters distance between them, but he could clearly hear the conversation between the villagers.

So that crater was a lake, huh... Wait. Wait, what?! I understood their words?! They can speak Japanese?!

Renji swallowed his breath in shock.

“We went around once but there was nothing. The sun will set soon, so let’s head back,” the village chief said, ushering the other villagers to move. They proceeded to leave briskly without noticing Renji’s presence. Once he confirmed that, Renji followed them at just a far enough distance not to lose sight of them.

Being able to speak Japanese is like the exact template of an other-world story, but I’m grateful. I don’t want to approach armed strangers, but if I can communicate with them then I may be able to negotiate something. At any rate, there’s no point in staying here. Whether I negotiate with them or not, I should at least follow them to get out of this forest.

Renji was almost certain that this was another world now. He decided he would follow the villagers until they left the forest.

◇　◇　◇

We only walked for a bit, but we got out of the forest pretty fast, surprisingly.

Renji had arrived at the edge of the forest. A hundred meters ahead of him were the villagers he had been following, and past them was the village they were heading towards. The village was surrounded by a rather tall fence to prevent intruders from getting in, and there was a gate as an entrance to the village.

They must be residents of that village.

From the sight of the poorly built wooden rooftops and their numbers, the population of the village was probably a few hundred or so people. The sun was already starting to set, so his only choice was to rely on the hospitality of the village or sleep outside.

I can guess what their standard of living is like from the look of their buildings, but I suppose it’d be better than sleeping outside. Well, I’ll have to make do. Renji decided on going to the village.

If I follow those guys into the village like this, they’ll realize I came out of the forest after them. It’d be an issue if they pried into why I was at the crater. I should move. With that thought, he took a detour. He distanced himself so the villagers wouldn’t spot him, then went around the outside of the village to the opposite side to the forest. The opposite side to the forest was farmland. The road towards the village cut through the farms, so he made his way to the road and through the gate, when—

“...”

He encountered a girl who appeared to be a villager. She must have been in her mid-teens—either the same age as Renji, or younger. The girl spotted him and froze at the sight of an unfamiliar stranger.

“Hey, are you one of the villagers here?” Renji marched right up to her.

“Yes, I am. Umm... Are you a noble?” the girl asked, looking at Renji’s face a little warily.

“No, I’m not a noble.”

“But you’re wearing fine clothes...”

“Hmm. So these look like fine clothes to you?” Renji looked down at the high school uniform he was wearing.

“They’re so clean... Only a noble would wear something like that.” The girl looked between his clothes and her own in comparison. Hers were rather worn out and dirtied by her daily work, looking rather shabby in Renji’s eyes.

Afterword

Hello everyone, this is Yuri Kitayama. Thank you for picking up Seirei Gensouki: Spirit Chronicles, Volume 14, Ballad of Vengeance—be it the regular version (no drama CD) or special edition (with drama CD).

The main story is the same in both the regular version and the special edition, but apart from the drama CD, they also differ in front cover—if you’ve only purchased one version, you can see the other cover on the HJ Bunko homepage!

Furthermore, the voice actors in the drama CD did a truly wonderful job. Just listening to them gave me the illusion that the characters were actually there. As the scenario writer, the casual snippet of their daily lives was even better than I imagined. Please give it a listen, everyone!

On top of Volume 2 of the drama CD, an official PV for Seirei Gensouki was created! The PV is narrated by Aishia’s voice actor, Yuki Kuwahara, who also read Aishia’s inserted lines in character. The difference in her voice during the narration and character lines was so dramatic, I had goosebumps while I observed the recording. Thank you so much, Ms. Kuwahara!

The official PV will be used in all kinds of promotion for the series from hereafter, so please give it a retweet if you see it on Twitter and spread the word. It’ll probably be uploaded to YouTube on the day Volume 14 goes on sale—August 1—so go check it out!

Since I’m running low on space, I’ll move on to discussing Volume 14. I’m sure there are some people who read the afterword first, so without any major spoilers: there was lots of foreshadowing in this volume, new twists added at the very end, and other things that may cause a huge shift in the story, don’t you think?

With that said, there are still plenty of plot twists up to Volume 10 that haven’t been addressed yet, and the ending I imagine for the series is still far away—I’d say we’ve taken one step into the middle stages of the story, perhaps? I plan on progressing the story and making it more exciting in the future, so I’d appreciate it if you could continue giving Seirei Gensouki your support.

And so, let’s meet again in Volume 15!

July 2019

Yuri Kitayama

Epilogue: Engagement

In the Beltrum Kingdom, in a certain room of the Rodania guest house, Sakata Hiroaki was seated beside Roanna, facing Duke Huguenot.

“One week has passed since Princess Christina and Princess Flora disappeared. And Vanessa hasn’t woken up yet, so we have no idea what happened. With no correspondence from the two of them, the Restoration has fallen into chaos. At this rate, the nobles may rebel and cause the organization to collapse. The Restoration is facing its greatest dilemma yet.”

Hence, they had to administer a powerful remedy to address this as soon as possible. Duke Huguenot explained the situation to Hiroaki with the gravest expression he’d ever had.

“Well, I suppose I get what you’re saying... But are you serious?”

Hiroaki crossed his arms with a peeved expression, then stared at Duke Huguenot with a discontent look. He’d witnessed the chaos of the Restoration from a close proximity this week, but he was unsure if he should just accept Duke Huguenot’s proposal.

“Yes. For form’s sake, Galarc Kingdom’s Third Princess Rosalie will be your first wife, and Roanna will be your second wife. I humbly ask that you agree to declaring these engagements as soon as possible.”

“Hmm. Rosalie will be thirteen next year...”

That would easily be a crime in Japan, right? While he didn’t say that out loud, even Hiroaki felt some reluctance towards marrying a girl of that age so easily. While he wasn’t entirely unwilling, if he was being entirely honest, he was hoping for one more reason to give him the final push.

There was one particular reason that came to mind, but it was against his beliefs to ask for it himself. Or rather, he feared what others would think of him if he did. Thus, he hadn’t tried to make a move himself until now.

But now that he thought about it, there was no better chance than this—it was possible he’d never have a better chance if he hesitated here.

That was why he resolved himself.

“...I have a condition,” he said coolly.

“What might that be?” Duke Huguenot bowed his head as though he was willing to accept anything.

Hiroaki cleared his throat and gave his condition. “It’s not really for me to negotiate, so I’ll leave that to you, but...I want Liselotte as my third wife. Can you make that happen?”